<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<Exam xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Properties>
    <Title>Practice Assessment for Exam MD-102: Endpoint Administrator</Title>
    <Code />
    <Version>3</Version>
    <Passmark>700</Passmark>
    <TimeLimit>180</TimeLimit>
    <Instructions />
  </Properties>
  <Sections>
    <Section>
      <Title>Main</Title>
      <Questions>
        <Question>
          <No>1</No>
          <Text>Your company has developed a custom line-of-business (LOB) app for the sales team. The app needs to be deployed to both company-owned and personal devices used by the sales team.

How should you deploy the LOB app using Intune while ensuring that corporate data within the app is protected?

Each correct answer presents part of the solution. What two actions should you perform?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>66</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Add the LOB app to Intune as a Line-of-business app.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Apply an app protection policy to the LOB app.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deploy the LOB app using Group Policy.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Require device enrollment for all personal devices.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use the Microsoft Store for Business to deploy the LOB app.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Adding the LOB app to Intune as a Line-of-business app (A) is correct because Intune allows centralized deployment to both company-owned and personal devices. Applying an app protection policy (B) ensures corporate data is secured through encryption and access controls without requiring full device enrollment. Group Policy (C) is incorrect as it’s not used for mobile devices. Requiring device enrollment (D) is unnecessary with app protection policies, and the Microsoft Store for Business (E) is for store apps, not custom LOB apps. [https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-applications/] &amp; [https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/apps-add]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>2</No>
          <Text>Your company has a diverse workforce using Windows, macOS, iOS, and Android devices. The IT department needs to ensure that all employees have access to Microsoft 365 Apps while maintaining data security and compliance.

How should you deploy Microsoft 365 Apps to all devices and ensure they are kept up-to-date automatically?

Each correct answer presents part of the solution. What two actions should you perform?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>67</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure policies for Office apps in Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deploy Microsoft 365 Apps as part of a Windows Autopilot deployment.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deploy Microsoft 365 Apps by using Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Manually update Microsoft 365 Apps on each device.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use Group Policy to manage Microsoft 365 Apps updates.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Configuring policies for Office apps in Intune (A) is correct because Intune can manage deployment, updates, and compliance for Microsoft 365 Apps across all platforms. Deploying Microsoft 365 Apps using Intune (C) is correct as it ensures the apps are automatically installed and updated on all supported devices (Windows, macOS, iOS, and Android). Deploying through Windows Autopilot (B) is incorrect because it only applies to new Windows devices. Manually updating apps (D) is inefficient, and Group Policy (E) doesn’t support all platforms. https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-applications/ &amp; https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/apps-add</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>3</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription that uses Microsoft Intune.

All devices are enrolled in Intune.

You plan to use Intune to deploy Microsoft 365 apps to all supported device platforms.

Which two device platforms support the app deployment? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>68</char>
            <char>69</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Android</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>iOS</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Linux</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>macOS</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Windows 11</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>If you want to add and deploy Microsoft 365 apps in Intune, you can select only the following two platforms: Windows 10 and later and macOS. https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/administer-endpoint-applications/ &amp; https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/apps-add-office365 &amp; https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/apps-add-office365-macos</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>4</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription that contains the following groups:

    Group1: Security group

    Group2: Microsoft 365 group

    Group3: Distribution group

The subscription contains devices that are enrolled in Microsoft Intune and have Microsoft 365 apps installed.

You need to configure the Microsoft 365 apps.

What is the maximum number of policies for Microsoft Office apps that you can create?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>3</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>5</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>6</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>64</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Policies for Office apps can have three scopes: all users, users that access documents anonymously by using Office on the web, or users in a specific group. You can create only one policy for all users and one policy for anonymous users. For users in a specific group, you can create a maximum of one policy per group, regardless of the group type. Because we have three groups, we can create maximum of five policies for Office apps – one for all users, one for anonymous users, and one for each group. https://learn.microsoft.com/deployoffice/admincenter/overview-cloud-policy</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>5</No>
          <Text>Your company has a diverse range of devices, including Windows, macOS, and Android. The company wants to ensure that all employees have access to necessary applications while maintaining security and compliance, using Microsoft Intune for device management.

How should you deploy Microsoft 365 Apps to all devices and configure the apps with specific organizational settings before users open them for the first time?

Each correct answer presents part of the solution. What two actions should you perform?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>66</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create an app configuration policy in Intune to configure the organizational settings.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deploy Microsoft 365 Apps using Intune and include the app configuration policy during enrollment.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Manually configure the organizational settings on each device after deploying Microsoft 365 Apps.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use Group Policy to deploy Microsoft 365 Apps and configure the settings.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Creating an app configuration policy in Intune (A) is correct because it ensures that organizational settings are pre-configured across all devices before users open the apps, ensuring consistency and compliance. Deploying Microsoft 365 Apps using Intune and including the app configuration policy during enrollment (B) is correct because it automates both app deployment and settings configuration across Windows, macOS, and Android devices. Manually configuring settings on each device (C) is incorrect because it's inefficient and doesn't scale well. Using Group Policy (D) is incorrect because it only applies to Windows devices and can't manage macOS or Android. https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-applications/ &amp; https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/fundamentals/manage-apps</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>6</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes a Windows device named Device1 that is enrolled in Microsoft Intune.

Device1 has the following configuration:

    OS Architecture: 64-bit

    Join Type: Microsoft Entra joined

    Enrollment Type: Intune enrolled

You purchase a new app named App1 that has the following configuration:

    Architecture: 32-bit

    IntuneWin file size: 9GB

You need to deploy App1 to Device1 by using Microsoft Intune.

What should you do first?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Download a 64-bit version of the source files.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text> Enable Co-management. </Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Microsoft Entra Hybrid Join the device.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Reduce the file size of the IntuneWin file.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>You should first reduce the file size of the IntuneWin file. The maximum size of an IntuneWin file for deploying a Win32 app is 8GB. https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-update-applications/4-manage-window-32-apps-intune</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>7</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes the following resources:

    A user named User1

    Two groups named Group1 and Group2

    A Windows 10 device named Device1

Device1 is a member of Group1. User1 is a member of Group2.

You deploy a new Windows 10 app named App1 to User1 on Device1 with the following assignments:

    Required: Group1

    Uninstall: Group2

When User1 signs into Device1, what is the status of App1 on the device?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>The app will be installed and will be available in the Company Portal.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>The app will be installed and will NOT be available in the Company Portal.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>The app will be uninstalled and will be available in the Company Portal.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>The app will be uninstalled and will NOT be available in the Company Portal.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>If an app is assigned as Required for a device and Uninstall for a user, the device setting will take precedence. The app is not assigned as available to any group so it will not appear as available. https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/apps-deploy</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>8</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 500 Windows 11 Enterprise devices that are managed by using Microsoft Intune.

You add an app named App1 to Microsoft Intune.

You need to ensure that App1 is automatically installed for all users.

What should you configure for App1?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>App Configuration policies</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>App settings</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Application assignments</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Application information</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>You need to configure the application assignments. For devices enrolled with Intune, the app will only be ‘pushed’ when groups are assigned as Required. https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/apps-deploy</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>9</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 500 Windows 11 Enterprise devices that are managed by using Microsoft Intune.

You plan to deploy Microsoft 365 Apps to the devices by using Intune.

You need to limit the diagnostic data that is sent to Microsoft for the Microsoft 365 Apps.

What should you create?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>a Microsoft 365 Apps for Windows 11 configuration</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>an App Configuration policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>an App Protection policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>an Office Apps policy</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Creating a policy using Administrative Templates allows you to configure various settings related to Office applications, including controlling the amount of diagnostic data sent to Microsoft. This is the most straightforward way to manage Office apps through Intune.</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>10</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription that uses Microsoft Intune.

All Android devices are enrolled in Intune.

You need to add Android apps to Intune.

For which app type should you first connect Intune to an Android Enterprise account?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text> Android Enterprise system app </Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Android store app</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>line-of-business app</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Managed Google Play app</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Managed Google Play is Google's enterprise app store and the sole source of applications for Android Enterprise in Intune. Before you can add Managed Google Play apps to Intune, you must connect the Intune tenant to Managed Google Play by using an Android Enterprise account. If this step is not performed, you will get the following error message: “Connect your Intune account to your Android Enterprise account to browse Managed Google Play. Click here to start connection process.” https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/apps-add-android-for-work</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>11</No>
          <Text>Your company is planning to deploy Microsoft 365 Apps to their Windows 11 devices using Intune. They want to ensure that all previous MSI versions of Office are removed during the deployment to avoid conflicts.

How should you configure the deployment to remove all existing MSI versions of Office from the devices?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deploy the Microsoft 365 Apps as a Win32 app to handle the removal of MSI versions.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enable the 'Remove MSI from end-user devices' option in the app suite configuration.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Manually uninstall all MSI versions of Office from each device before deploying Microsoft 365 Apps.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use a PowerShell script to remove MSI versions of Office before deploying Microsoft 365 Apps.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Enabling the 'Remove MSI from end-user devices' option in the app suite configuration (B) is correct because Intune offers this built-in option during the configuration of Microsoft 365 Apps. By enabling this, all previous MSI versions of Office are automatically removed during the deployment, ensuring a seamless installation without conflicts. Deploying the Microsoft 365 Apps as a Win32 app (A) is incorrect because it doesn’t specifically handle the removal of MSI versions, and there’s no need to use this approach when Intune provides a dedicated setting for removing MSI versions. Manually uninstalling all MSI versions of Office from each device (C) is incorrect because it is inefficient and labor-intensive, especially when this can be automated through Intune. Using a PowerShell script (D) is also unnecessary because the built-in option in Intune handles MSI removal during the deployment process without the need for custom scripting. https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/administer-endpoint-applications/4-deploy-microsoft-365-apps-intune &amp; https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-applications/3-add-apps-intune &amp; https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/apps-add-office365</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>12</No>
          <Text>Your company has recently migrated to Microsoft Intune to manage their endpoint devices. They have a mix of Windows 10 and Windows 11 devices and need to deploy a critical line-of-business (LOB) application packaged as a Win32 app. The application must be installed on all devices in the Sales department.

How should you ensure that the application is deployed and kept up to date automatically?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deploy the application using Group Policy and assign it to the Sales department OU.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Manually install the application on each device and configure Windows Update to keep it updated.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use the Intune Management Extension to deploy the Win32 app and configure it as a required app for the Sales department group.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use the Microsoft Store for Business to deploy the application and assign it to the Sales department group.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Using the Intune Management Extension to deploy the Win32 app and configure it as a required app for the Sales department group (C) is correct because Intune’s Management Extension is designed specifically to handle the deployment and management of Win32 apps in a cloud-based environment. By configuring the app as "required," Intune will automatically deploy the app and keep it updated on all devices assigned to the Sales department group, ensuring seamless management. Deploying the application using Group Policy (A) is incorrect because Group Policy is typically used for on-premises environments and does not align with Intune’s cloud-based management approach. Manually installing the application and using Windows Update to keep it updated (B) is incorrect because it contradicts the goal of automating both the deployment and update process, and Windows Update cannot manage updates for Win32 apps. Using the Microsoft Store for Business (D) is incorrect because it is designed to deploy Universal Windows Platform (UWP) apps, not traditional Win32 line-of-business applications. https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-applications/ &amp; https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/store-apps-microsoft</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>13</No>
          <Text>Your company has recently deployed Microsoft Intune to manage their mobile devices and applications. They have a mix of iOS and Android devices used by employees for both personal and work tasks. The IT department wants to ensure that corporate data is protected while allowing employees to use their devices for personal purposes.

You need to configure app protection policies to secure corporate data on these devices without requiring device enrollment.

Each correct answer presents part of the solution. Which three actions should you perform?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>66</char>
            <char>67</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Assign the MAM policy to the user groups.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure app protection settings for managed apps.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a Mobile Application Management (MAM) policy in Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enroll all devices in Intune using Mobile Device Management (MDM).</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Require users to install the Company Portal app.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Assigning the MAM policy to the user groups (A) is correct because Mobile Application Management (MAM) policies target users, ensuring that only those in specific user groups are required to comply with the app protection policies. This method protects corporate data while allowing users to retain personal control over their devices. Configuring app protection settings for managed apps (B) is correct because these settings allow you to enforce security measures, such as data encryption, preventing data sharing between personal and corporate apps, and requiring PINs for access, protecting corporate data within specific apps. Creating a Mobile Application Management (MAM) policy in Intune (C) is correct because MAM allows you to secure corporate data without enrolling personal devices in Mobile Device Management (MDM), ensuring that corporate data is protected at the app level. Enrolling all devices in Intune using MDM (D) is incorrect because MDM involves full device management, which is unnecessary for this scenario and contradicts the goal of allowing personal use of devices. Requiring users to install the Company Portal app (E) is incorrect for MAM without enrollment since it’s not needed to apply MAM policies. https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/administer-endpoint-applications/2-manage-apps-intune &amp; https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-applications/2-deploy-applications-intune &amp; https://learn.microsoft.com/microsoft-365/solutions/apps-config-overview?view=o365-worldwide</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>14</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription that uses Microsoft Intune.

You have the following devices enrolled in Intune:

    Device1: Windows 11

    Device2: Android

    Device3: iOS

You plan to create an app configuration policy named Config1 in Intune.

To which devices can you apply Config1?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 and Device2 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 and Device3 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2 and Device3</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device2 and Device3 only</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>You can create and use app configuration policies to provide configuration settings for both iOS/iPadOS apps and Android apps. These configuration settings allow an app to be customized by using app configuration and management. https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/app-configuration-policies-overview &amp; https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/administer-endpoint-applications/</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>15</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription that uses Microsoft Intune.

You have the following devices:

    Device1: Windows 11 device enrolled in Intune

    Device2: Android device enrolled in Intune

    Device3: Android device NOT enrolled in Intune

    Device4: iOS device NOT enrolled in Intune

To which devices can you apply an app configuration policy?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 and Device2 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2, Device3 and Device4</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text> Device2, Device3 and Device4 only </Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device3 and Device4 only</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>By using an app configuration policy, you can provide configuration settings to both iOS/iPadOS apps and Android apps. You can provide the settings regardless of whether the devices are enrolled in Intune or not. https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/app-configuration-policies-overview &amp; https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/administer-endpoint-applications/</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>16</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that uses Microsoft Intune.

You plan to implement a bring your own device (BYOD) policy to support iOS and Android devices.

You need to ensure that users can access all Microsoft 365 Apps on their devices. The solution must meet the following requirements:

    Prevent users copying and pasting information from Microsoft 365 apps to non-Microsoft apps.

    Private devices must not be enrolled to Microsoft Intune.

What should you configure?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>a Conditional Access policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>a Device Restriction policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>an App Protection policy </Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>an App Configuration policy</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>An App Protection policy allows you to disable copy and paste between applications. With Conditional Access policies you cannot configure the ‘app behavior’ and a Restriction policy or Configuration policy do not meet all of the requirements. https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-ios</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>17</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes iOS and Android devices that are managed by using Microsoft Intune.

You need to prevent users printing Microsoft Word documents stored in Microsoft 365 from their mobile devices by using an app protection policy.

Which settings should you configure?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Access requirements</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Conditional Access Policies</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Conditional launch </Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Data Protection</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>The Data Protection setting has an option to prevent printing of organizational data (set to block, default is allowed). https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/app-protection-policy-settings-android</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>18</No>
          <Text>Your company has developed a custom Line of Business (LOB) application that needs to be protected by Intune App Protection Policies. The application is simple and does not have built-in data protection features.

How can you enable app protection for this LOB application without modifying its source code?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enroll the devices using the application into Intune MDM.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Integrate the Intune App SDK into the application.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Publish the application to the Apple App Store or Google Play Store.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use the Intune App Wrapping Tool to wrap the application.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Using the Intune App Wrapping Tool to wrap the application (D) is correct because it enables the application of Intune app protection policies without modifying the source code, effectively securing the LOB app. Enrolling the devices using the application into Intune MDM (A) is incorrect as it focuses on device management, not app protection. Integrating the Intune App SDK (B) is incorrect because it requires changes to the app's source code. Publishing the application to app stores (C) does not apply app protection policies and is not relevant to securing the app. https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/execute-mobile-application-management/ &amp; https://learn.microsoft.com/microsoft-365/solutions/manage-devices-with-intune-app-protection?view=o365-worldwide</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>19</No>
          <Text>Your company has a mix of corporate-owned and BYOD (Bring Your Own Device) devices used by employees to access company data. The IT department wants to ensure that corporate data is protected on both managed and unmanaged devices without affecting personal data.

How should you implement a solution that protects corporate data at the app level while allowing employees to use their devices for personal tasks?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deploy a VPN solution to secure all device communications.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Implement Intune App Protection Policies (APP) for both managed and unmanaged devices.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Require all devices to be enrolled in Intune MDM.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use Microsoft Defender for Endpoint to monitor all devices.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Implementing Intune App Protection Policies (APP) for both managed and unmanaged devices (B) is correct because it allows you to secure corporate data within apps without affecting personal data on BYOD devices. Deploying a VPN solution (A) is incorrect as it secures communications but does not protect data at the app level. Requiring all devices to be enrolled in Intune MDM (C) contradicts the goal of allowing personal use without full device management. Using Microsoft Defender for Endpoint (D) is incorrect because it focuses on endpoint security rather than specific app-level data protection. https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/execute-mobile-application-management/ &amp; https://learn.microsoft.com/microsoft-365/solutions/manage-devices-with-intune-app-protection?view=o365-worldwide</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>20</No>
          <Text>Your company is rolling out a new mobile application for its sales team. The application needs to be configured to prevent data leakage by restricting copy-and-paste functions and ensuring that company data cannot be saved to personal storage locations. The sales team uses a mix of iOS and Android devices, both managed and unmanaged.

What two actions should you perform to implement the necessary configurations to meet these requirements?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>66</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create an app protection policy in Microsoft Intune to prevent saving company data to personal storage locations.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create an app protection policy in Microsoft Intune to restrict copy-and-paste functions.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deploy the app protection policy only to managed devices.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Instruct the sales team to manually configure their devices to restrict copy-and-paste functions.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Creating app protection policies in Microsoft Intune to restrict copy-and-paste functions (A) is correct because it directly prevents users from copying corporate data to personal applications, protecting sensitive information. Similarly, preventing saving company data to personal storage locations (B) ensures that corporate data remains within managed applications, further mitigating data leakage risks. Instructing the sales team to manually configure their devices (C) is inefficient and prone to errors, which could lead to compliance issues. Deploying the policy only to managed devices (D) would be inadequate as it would not cover unmanaged devices, leaving gaps in data protection across the sales team's devices. https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/execute-mobile-application-management/ &amp; https://learn.microsoft.com/microsoft-365/solutions/manage-devices-with-intune-app-protection?view=o365-worldwide</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>21</No>
          <Text>Your company has implemented Microsoft Intune to manage mobile devices and applications. With a mix of corporate-owned and BYOD (Bring Your Own Device) devices accessing sensitive company data, the IT department is concerned about data leakage and wants to ensure that only approved apps can access this data.

What three actions should you perform to configure app protection policies that prevent data leakage and ensure that only approved apps can access company data?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>66</char>
            <char>69</char>
            <char>70</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Block legacy authentication capable iOS and Android apps.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create an app protection policy for iOS and Android devices.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deploy a VPN solution for all mobile devices.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enable multi-factor authentication for all users.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Implement Conditional Access policies to require approved client apps.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>70</Alphabet>
              <Text>Require device enrollment for all BYOD devices.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Creating an app protection policy for iOS and Android devices (B) is correct because it restricts access to sensitive corporate data to approved apps, preventing data leakage. Implementing Conditional Access policies to require approved client apps (E) ensures that only secure applications can access corporate data, enhancing protection. Requiring device enrollment for all BYOD devices (F) allows the organization to manage security policies effectively, ensuring secure access to corporate data. Blocking legacy authentication (A), deploying a VPN (C), and enabling multi-factor authentication (D) do not directly address app-level data protection. https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/execute-mobile-application-management/ &amp; https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/app-protection-framework</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>22</No>
          <Text>Your company has recently deployed Microsoft Intune to manage their fleet of iOS devices. They want to ensure that only corporate accounts can be used within Microsoft Office apps on these devices, blocking any personal accounts.

What two actions should you perform to configure the app protection policy to meet this requirement?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>68</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Assign the app protection policy to all users.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text> Create a Conditional Access policy to block personal accounts.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enable multi-factor authentication for all users.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Set the IntuneMAMAllowedAccountsOnly key to Enabled in the app configuration policy.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Set the IntuneMAMUPN key to {{userprincipalname}} in the app configuration policy.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Assigning the app protection policy to all users (A) is correct as it ensures that the policy is enforced across all users accessing Microsoft Office apps on iOS devices. Setting the IntuneMAMAllowedAccountsOnly key to Enabled (D) is correct because it restricts usage to corporate accounts, blocking personal accounts. Creating a Conditional Access policy to block personal accounts (B) is incorrect because it doesn't enforce app-level restrictions. Enabling multi-factor authentication (C) does not prevent personal account use. Setting the IntuneMAMUPN key (E) identifies users but does not enforce account restrictions. https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-applications/11-assign-apps-company-employees &amp; https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/execute-mobile-application-management/5-implement-mobile-application-management-policies-intune</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>23</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription that contains a Microsoft Entra tenant. The tenant contains the following devices:

    Device1: Microsoft Entra joined Windows 11 device

    Device2: Microsoft Entra registered Windows 11 device

    Device3: Microsoft Entra joined Windows 10 device

    Device4: Microsoft Entra registered iOS device

Which devices can be activated by using subscription activation?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 and Device2 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 and Device3 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2, and Device3 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2, Device3, and Device4</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>To be able to use subscription activation, devices must be Microsoft Entra joined or hybrid Microsoft Entra joined. Workgroup-joined or Microsoft Entra registered devices are not supported. As such, you can use subscription activation only with Device1 and Device3. [MD-102 2-Implement dynamic deployment methods - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/implement-dynamic-deployment/] &amp; [Windows subscription activation - Windows Deployment | Microsoft Learn:  https://learn.microsoft.com/windows/deployment/windows-10-subscription-activation]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>24</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription that uses Microsoft Intune.

You have a device named Device1 that runs Windows 11. Device1 contains a variety of installed software and applications.

You need to reprovision Device1 and ensure that the device only contains the default Windows 11 installation. The solution must minimize administrative effort.

What should you use?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Microsoft Deployment Toolkit (MDT)</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Sysprep</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>User State Migration Tool (USMT)</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Windows Autopilot</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Windows Autopilot Reset takes the device back to a business-ready state, allowing the next user to sign in and get productive quickly and simply. Specifically, Windows Autopilot Reset: Removes personal files, apps, and settings &amp; Reapplies a device's original settings &amp; Sets the region, language, and keyboard to the original values &amp; Maintains the device's identity connection to Microsoft Entra ID &amp; Maintains the device's management connection to Intune. [MD-102 1-Deploy Devices using Windows Autopilot - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-devices-windows-autopilot/] &amp; [Windows Autopilot Reset | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/autopilot/windows-autopilot-reset]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>25</No>
          <Text>You purchase five devices that run Windows 11. Each device contains custom applications.

You need to remove the custom applications from each device. The solution must minimize administrative effort.

What should you use?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Sysprep</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>User State Migration Tool (USMT)</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Windows Configuration Designer</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Windows System Image Manager (Windows SIM)</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Windows Configuration Designer is used for creating provisioning packages. One of the options when creating a provisioning package is to remove preinstalled software. [MD-102 2-Implement dynamic deployment methods - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/implement-dynamic-deployment/] &amp; [Provisioning packages overview - Configure Windows | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/windows/configuration/provisioning-packages/provisioning-packages]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>26</No>
          <Text>You have 100 Windows 10 devices.

You need to upgrade the devices to Windows 11. The solution must meet the following requirements:

    Ensure that only local user documents that have been accessed in the last 90 days on each device are retained.

    Minimize administrative effort.

Which two should you include in the solution? Each correct answer presents part of the solution.</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>67</char>
            <char>68</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>In-Place Upgrade</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>OneDrive for Business</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>User State Migration Tool</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Windows Autopilot</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Windows Autopilot and User State Migration Tool are correct. Windows Autopilot will remove all user profiles and files from the local device and the User State Migration Tool will capture and migrate user accounts, user files, OS settings and application settings and can be configured to limit what is retains. [Examine desktop deployment - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/examine-enterprise-desktop/5-examine-desktop-deployment] &amp; [User State Migration Tool (USMT) - Getting Started (Windows 10) - Windows Deployment | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/windows/deployment/usmt/getting-started-with-the-user-state-migration-tool]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>27</No>
          <Text>You have a Workgroup joined device named Device1 that runs Windows 10 Professional and includes a user named User1.

You create a Microsoft 365 account for User1 and assign them a Windows 10 Enterprise E3 license.

You need to upgrade Device1 to Windows 10 Enterprise. The solution must minimize administrative effort.

What should you do?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Join Device1 to Microsoft Entra ID.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Perform a device reset.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Perform an in-place upgrade.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Reimage the device with a corporate Windows 10 Enterprise image.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Joining the device to Microsoft Entra ID and signing into the device will automatically upgrade it to Windows 10 Enterprise. [Deploy Windows Enterprise licenses - Windows Deployment | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/windows/deployment/deploy-enterprise-licenses]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>28</No>
          <Text>Your company is deploying new Windows 11 devices using Windows Autopilot. They want to ensure that the deployment process is seamless for end users, requiring minimal interaction during the Out-of-Box Experience (OOBE).

How should you configure the deployment to achieve a zero-touch installation (ZTI) experience?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure Autopilot profiles to automatically join devices to Azure AD and enroll in Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a custom Windows image with pre-installed applications and drivers.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Require users to manually complete the OOBE setup.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use Configuration Manager to deploy the Windows 11 image.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Configuring Autopilot profiles to automatically join devices to Azure AD and enroll in Intune (A) is correct because this enables Windows Autopilot to automate the deployment process and achieve a zero-touch installation (ZTI) experience with minimal user interaction during the Out-of-Box Experience (OOBE). Creating a custom Windows image with pre-installed applications and drivers (B) is incorrect because it does not leverage Autopilot’s capabilities for automation and still requires more manual effort. Requiring users to manually complete the OOBE setup (C) is incorrect because it contradicts the goal of a zero-touch installation by involving the user. Using Configuration Manager to deploy the Windows 11 image (D) is incorrect because while it can manage OS deployments, it does not provide the seamless, automated experience that Autopilot offers. [Explore readiness tools - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deployment-readiness/3-explore-readiness-tools] &amp; [Use Autopilot for modern deployment - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-devices-windows-autopilot/2-use-autopilot-for-modern-deployment] &amp; [Plan for Windows 11 | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/windows/whats-new/windows-11-plan]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>29</No>
          <Text>Your company is deploying new Windows 11 devices to its remote workforce. They want to ensure that these devices are pre-configured with necessary applications, settings, and policies before being delivered to employees.

How should you implement a deployment strategy to ensure the devices are business-ready upon delivery?

Each correct answer presents a complete solution. What are three possible ways to achieve this goal?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>66</char>
            <char>67</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use Windows Autopilot to automatically configure and enroll the devices into Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use Microsoft Intune to deploy PowerShell scripts that remove unnecessary built-in apps.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create and deploy device compliance policies in Intune to ensure security settings are applied.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a manual deployment process for each device, configuring settings on-site.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use Windows Server Update Services (WSUS) to push out applications and updates.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Using Windows Autopilot to automatically configure and enroll the devices into Intune (A) is correct because Autopilot provides a zero-touch deployment experience, ensuring that devices are pre-configured with necessary applications, settings, and policies, which is essential for a streamlined deployment to remote workers. Using Microsoft Intune to deploy PowerShell scripts that remove unnecessary built-in apps (B) is also correct because Intune can be used to automate the removal of unwanted software, simplifying the configuration process and ensuring devices are business-ready. Creating and deploying device compliance policies in Intune (C) is correct because it ensures that devices meet the required security settings and compliance standards before being handed over to employees. Creating a manual deployment process (D) is incorrect because it adds unnecessary administrative overhead and does not meet the goal of automating the deployment. Using WSUS to push out applications and updates (E) is incorrect because WSUS is primarily used for managing updates, not for configuring devices during initial deployment. [Evaluate upgrades and migrations in modern transitioning - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/plan-transition-modern-endpoint-management/5-evaluate-upgrades-migrations-modern-transitioning] &amp; [Explore readiness tools - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deployment-readiness/3-explore-readiness-tools] &amp; [Prepare for Windows 11 | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/windows/whats-new/windows-11-prepare]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>30</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes a group named Group1 and two devices named Device1 and Device2.

Device1 runs Windows 10 Enterprise and is a member of Group1. Device2 runs Windows 11 Professional.

You create a new Windows 10 Configuration Profile and configure the following assignments:

    Included Groups: All Devices

    Excluded Groups: Group1

You configure the follow applicability rule:

    Rule: Assign profile if

    Property: OS edition

    Value: Windows 10/11 Enterprise

Which devices will receive the profile?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 and Device2</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device2 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>neither Device1 nor Device2</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Device1 will not receive the profile as it is a member of Group1 which is excluded from the profile scope. Device2 will not receive the profile as it does not meet the Applicability Rules. [Create device profiles in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/configuration/device-profile-create]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>31</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription.

You purchase a device named Device1 and enroll Device1 in Microsoft Intune.

You need to configure Device1 to automatically login and display a single web app. The solution must ensure that only administrators are able to access other features on the device.

What should you configure?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>a Compliance policy using custom compliance JSON settings</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>a Compliance policy using kiosk mode</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>a Configuration profile using custom compliance JSON settings</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>a Configuration profile using kiosk mode</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>A Configuration profile using kiosk mode is correct. Kiosk mode is configured to allow access from a device to a single app. This is configured through Configuration profiles. [Kiosk settings for Windows and Holographic devices in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/configuration/kiosk-settings]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>32</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription that uses Microsoft Intune.

The following devices have Microsoft 365 apps installed and are enrolled in Intune:

    Device1: Windows 11

    Device2: Android

    Device3: iOS

You plan to use a Microsoft 365 Apps for enterprise security baseline named Baseline1.

To which devices can you apply Baseline1?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 and Device2 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 and Device3 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2 and Device3</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 only</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>The Microsoft 365 Apps for enterprise security baseline can be applied only to Windows 10 and later. When you are creating a profile by using a Microsoft 365 Apps for enterprise security baseline, the platform is set to Windows 10 and later, cannot be changed. [MD-102 Administer endpoint applications - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/administer-endpoint-applications/] &amp; [Security baseline for Microsoft 365 Apps for enterprise - Deploy Office | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/deployoffice/security/security-baseline]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>33</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 100 Windows 10 devices that are enrolled to Microsoft Intune.

You need to encrypt the Operating System volume of the Windows 10 devices. The solution must minimize administrative effort.

What should you use?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>BitLocker</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Encrypting File System</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Microsoft Defender for Endpoint</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Windows Information Protection</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>BitLocker supports encryption of all data that is stored on a Windows operating system volume and configured data volumes. [Explore Encrypting File System in Windows client - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/implement-device-data-protection/5-explore-encrypting-file-system-windows-client]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>34</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 500 Windows 11 Enterprise devices that are managed by using Microsoft Intune and Endpoint Protection.

You need to identify any devices that have been infected with viruses.

Which report should you review?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Antivirus agent status</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Detected malware</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device status</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Endpoint analytics</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>The Detected malware report provides the malware state of your organization’s devices. This report shows the number of devices with detected malware, as well as the malware details. [Microsoft Intune reports - Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/fundamentals/reports#detected-malware-report-organizational]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>35</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 100 Windows devices that are enrolled in Microsoft Intune.

You need to ensure that a group of test devices are updated to Windows 11 version 23H2. The solution must ensure that the test devices do NOT receive feature updates for at least two years.

What should you configure?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Compliance policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configuration profile</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Feature Update policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Update Ring</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>A Feature Update policy will update devices to a specific version and new updates will not be installed until the policy is modified or removed. [Configure feature updates policy for Windows 10 Windows 11 devices in Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/windows-10-feature-updates]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>36</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes the following devices:

    Device1: Windows 10 Pro version 22H2

    Device2: Windows 11 Pro version 23H2

    Device3: Windows 11 Home version 23H2

    Device4: Windows 11 Enterprise version 22H2

You need to manage updates for the Windows devices by using update rings in Microsoft Intune.

Which devices can be managed by using Microsoft Intune?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device3 and Device4 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device2, Device3, and Device4 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2, and Device4 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device4 only</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Windows 10/11 Pro, Windows 10/11 Enterprise, Windows 10/11 Team - for Surface Hub devices, Windows Holographic for Business, and Windows 10/11 Enterprise LTSC are Windows editions that are supported for Update Ring policies. [Configure Update rings for Windows 10 and later policy in Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/windows-10-update-rings]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>37</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 50 corporate iOS devices that are enrolled in Microsoft Intune.

You need to ensure that iOS updates are deferred for 90 days. The solution must prevent users manually installing updates during the 90-day period.

What should you configure?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Compliance policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configuration profile</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Update policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Update Ring profile</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>A Configuration profile can be configured to delay the visibility of software updates for up to 90 days. [Use Microsoft Intune to manage software updates for supervised iOS/iPadOS devices | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/software-updates-ios]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>38</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 500 Windows 10 Enterprise 22H2 devices that are managed by using Microsoft Intune.

You need to update the devices to Windows 11. The solution must ensure that users can postpone the update for a maximum of two weeks.

What should you configure first?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device configuration profile</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Feature update policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Quality update profile</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Update ring policy</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>An Update ring policy allows you to update to Windows 11.Though the Feature update policy does allow that as well, only an Update Ring allows you to postpone updates. Quality update profiles and Device configuration profiles do not allow you to update the devices to Windows 11. [Configure Update rings for Windows 10 and later policy in Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/windows-10-update-rings] &amp; [Configure feature updates policy for Windows 10 Windows 11 devices in Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/windows-10-feature-updates]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>39</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 500 Windows 10 Enterprise 22H2 devices that are managed by using Microsoft Intune.

You plan to update the devices to Windows 11.

You need to identify the devices that do NOT meet the requirements for Windows 11.

What report should you review?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>All devices report</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device Compliance report</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Windows feature update device compatibility risks report</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Windows feature update device readiness report</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>The Windows feature update device readiness report shows devices with their readiness status. The Windows feature update compatibility risks reports shows this for each application or driver, but it does not display this information per device. The All devices report and the Device Compliance report do not display this information. [Use Windows compatibility reports for Windows 10 and Windows 11 updates in Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/windows-update-compatibility-reports]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>40</No>
          <Text>Your company has a geographically distributed workforce and wants to simplify device provisioning for remote users. They are considering using Microsoft Entra ID and Intune for device management.

You need to choose a provisioning method that minimizes user interaction during the setup process and allows IT to preconfigure devices before shipping them to users.

Which provisioning method should you choose?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Bulk enrollment</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Manual configuration by IT</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Self-service in OOBE/Settings</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Windows Autopilot</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Windows Autopilot allows IT to preconfigure devices, minimizing user interaction during setup. Self-service in OOBE/Settings requires more user interaction. Bulk enrollment is more suitable for admin-driven deployment but still requires some user interaction. Manual configuration by IT is not efficient for a geographically distributed workforce. [Manage device authentication - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/administer-device-authentication/] &amp; [Plan your Microsoft Entra join deployment - Microsoft Entra ID | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/entra/identity/devices/device-join-plan]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>41</No>
          <Text>Your company has recently transitioned to a cloud-first strategy and wants to streamline the deployment of new devices. They aim to reduce the time and effort required for IT staff to configure devices manually.

You need to implement a solution that allows users to self-enroll their devices while ensuring compliance with corporate policies.

What should you recommend?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deploy a custom imaging solution for all new devices.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Implement Microsoft Entra join and configure Intune for automatic enrollment.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Require users to manually configure their devices using a provided checklist.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use a third-party MDM solution to manage device compliance.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Implementing Microsoft Entra join and configuring Intune for automatic enrollment allows users to self-enroll their devices while ensuring compliance with corporate policies. Requiring users to manually configure their devices or deploying a custom imaging solution does not streamline the process. Using a third-party MDM solution is unnecessary when Intune can provide the required functionality. [Examine Microsoft Entra join prerequisites limitations and benefits - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/administer-device-authentication/3-examine-azure-active-directory-join-prerequisites-limitations-benefits] &amp; [What are Microsoft Entra registered devices? - Microsoft Entra ID | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/entra/identity/devices/concept-device-registration] &amp; [Manage devices remotely - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/enroll-devices-use-intune/11-manage-devices-remotely] &amp; [Examine prerequisites for co-management - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/plan-transition-modern-endpoint-management/3-examine-prerequisites-for-co-management] &amp; [Manage devices in Microsoft Entra ID using the Microsoft Entra admin center - Microsoft Entra ID | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/entra/identity/devices/manage-device-identities]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>42</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription.

You purchase the following devices:

    Device1: Windows 11

    Device2: Windows 10

    Device3: Android

    Device4: iOS

You plan to manage all the devices by using Microsoft Intune.

Which devices can be Microsoft Entra joined, and then automatically enrolled in Intune?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 and Device2 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2, and Device3 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2, and Device4 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2, Device3, and Device4 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 only</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Only Windows devices can be enrolled in Intune automatically by joining the devices to Microsoft Entra ID. Only Windows devices support this feature, as only Windows devices can be Microsoft Entra joined. [Enroll Devices Using Microsoft Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/enroll-devices-use-intune/] &amp; [Enable MDM automatic enrollment for Windows | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/enrollment/windows-enroll]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>43</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription that uses Microsoft Intune.

You plan to create an Intune device limit restriction named Restriction1.

You need to set the maximum number of devices that a user can enroll.

What is the maximum number of devices that you can specify in Restriction1?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>15</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>30</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>50</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>100</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Intune device limit restrictions set the maximum number of devices that a user can enroll. You can allow a user to enroll up to 15 devices. [Enroll devices using Microsoft Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/enroll-devices-use-intune/] &amp; [Understand Intune and Microsoft Entra device limit restrictions - Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/enrollment/device-limit-intune-azure]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>44</No>
          <Text>Your company has recently purchased a batch of iOS devices through Apple Business Manager and wants to ensure that these devices are automatically enrolled in Microsoft Intune as soon as users turn them on.

You need to configure the enrollment settings for these iOS devices.

Each correct answer contributes to the solution. Which two actions should you perform?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>67</char>
            <char>69</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Assign a device configuration profile to the iOS devices in Microsoft Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Manually enroll the devices in Microsoft Intune using the Company Portal app.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create an MDM server profile in Apple Business Manager and download the server token.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enable device-based conditional access policies for the iOS devices</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Upload the MDM server token to Microsoft Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Creating an MDM server profile in Apple Business Manager and downloading the server token (C) is essential to enable automatic enrollment of iOS devices into Microsoft Intune. Uploading the MDM server token to Microsoft Intune (E) ensures that the devices are automatically enrolled when powered on. Assigning a device configuration profile (A) and enabling device-based conditional access policies (D) do not manage the enrollment process. Manually enrolling devices using the Company Portal app (B) is a manual process and not suitable for automated enrollment. [Enroll devices using Microsoft Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/enroll-devices-use-intune/] &amp; [Tutorial - Use Apple Business Manager to enroll iOS/iPadOS devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/enrollment/tutorial-use-device-enrollment-program-enroll-ios]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>45</No>
          <Text>Your company uses Microsoft Intune to manage a mix of corporate-owned and BYOD devices. The company wants to ensure that only compliant devices can access Microsoft 365 services, such as email and SharePoint Online, while allowing users to work from any device and location.

You need to configure a solution that ensures only compliant devices can access Microsoft 365 services.

What should you do?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure a device configuration profile in Intune to enforce compliance settings.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a Conditional Access policy in Microsoft Entra ID that requires device compliance for accessing Microsoft 365 services.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deploy an app protection policy in Intune to manage access to Microsoft 365 apps.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text> Set up a device enrollment restriction policy in Intune to block non-compliant devices. </Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Creating a Conditional Access policy in Microsoft Entra ID that requires device compliance (B) is the correct solution because it ensures that only compliant devices can access Microsoft 365 services like email and SharePoint Online. Configuring a device configuration profile in Intune (A) enforces device settings but does not control access to services based on compliance. Deploying an app protection policy (C) helps manage data protection within apps, but it does not enforce compliance for accessing services. Setting up a device enrollment restriction policy in Intune (D) only controls device enrollment and does not manage access to Microsoft 365 services for compliant devices. [MD-102 3-Implement device compliance - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/implement-device-compliance/] &amp; [Use Conditional Access with Microsoft Intune compliance policies - Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/conditional-access]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>46</No>
          <Text>Your company is using Microsoft Intune to manage their devices. They want to ensure that all devices accessing Exchange Online mailboxes comply with their security policies.

How should you configure the devices to implement this compliance policy?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a compliance policy that requires devices to have antivirus software installed.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a compliance policy that requires devices to have the latest OS updates installed.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a Conditional Access policy that requires multifactor authentication for all users.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a Conditional Access policy that targets Exchange Online and requires device compliance.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Creating a Conditional Access policy that targets Exchange Online and requires device compliance (D) is the correct solution because it ensures that only compliant devices, as defined by your Intune compliance policies, can access Exchange Online mailboxes. Creating a compliance policy that requires antivirus software (A) or the latest OS updates (B) helps improve security, but these actions do not enforce compliance specifically for Exchange Online. Creating a Conditional Access policy that requires multifactor authentication (C) enhances security but does not ensure device compliance for accessing Exchange Online. [MD-102 3-Implement device compliance - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/implement-device-compliance/] &amp; [Building a Conditional Access policy - Microsoft Entra ID | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/entra/identity/conditional-access/concept-conditional-access-policies]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>47</No>
          <Text>Your company is migrating from legacy LAPS to Windows LAPS for their hybrid-joined devices. They want to ensure a smooth transition without disruptions to the OS deployment workflow.

How should you configure the devices to mitigate potential disruptions caused by immediate password modifications during the OS deployment workflow?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Apply the Windows LAPS policy after the OS deployment workflow is complete.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure the Windows LAPS policy to target the same account used by the OS deployment workflow.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text> Disable Windows LAPS during the OS deployment workflow. </Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use a clean staging Organizational Unit (OU) that does not apply a Windows LAPS policy.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Applying the Windows LAPS policy after the OS deployment workflow is complete (A) is the correct solution because it prevents any password resets from occurring during the deployment process, ensuring a smooth workflow without disruptions. Configuring the Windows LAPS policy to target the same account used by the OS deployment (B) is incorrect, as it can cause conflicts if the account’s password is modified during the deployment. Disabling Windows LAPS during the OS deployment workflow (C) is not ideal, as it introduces security risks and additional management overhead. Using a clean staging Organizational Unit (OU) without a Windows LAPS policy (D) is technically correct but adds unnecessary complexity to the deployment process when simply applying the LAPS policy afterward is a more efficient solution. [Describe Microsoft Entra join - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/administer-device-authentication/2-describe-azure-active-directory-join] &amp; [Examine prerequisites for co-management - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/plan-transition-modern-endpoint-management/3-examine-prerequisites-for-co-management] &amp; [Get started with Windows LAPS deployment and migration scenarios | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/windows-server/identity/laps/laps-scenarios-deployment-migration]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>48</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that contains 500 devices and that uses Microsoft Intune.

You deploy Microsoft Intune Compliance Policies to the subscription.

You notice that when a device is not assigned a Compliance policy, it is marked as compliant in Intune.

You need to ensure that devices that do NOT have an assigned compliance policy assigned are marked as non-compliant.

What should you configure?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Conditional Access policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Intune Compliance policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Intune Compliance Policy settings</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Intune Tenant Administration settings</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>The Intune Compliance Policy settings allow for the configuration of the setting Mark devices with no compliance policy assigned as Non-Compliant. [Device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/device-compliance-get-started]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>49</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription.

You need to prevent users from connecting to the subscription when they are using jailbroken devices.

What two settings should you configure? Each correct answer presents part of the solution.</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>66</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>a Conditional Access policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>a Device Compliance policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>a Device Configuration profile</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>a Device enrollment manager</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>a Device type restriction</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>A Device Compliance Policy and a Conditional Access Policy is correct. A Device Compliance Policy can be configured to mark jailbroken devices as non-compliant, and a Conditional Access policy can then block these devices. [Device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/device-compliance-get-started]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>50</No>
          <Text>Your company has a mix of Windows, iOS, and Android devices. They want to ensure that all devices accessing their corporate network are compliant with their security policies, including encryption and password protection.

How should you configure the devices to ensure that only compliant devices can access the corporate network?

Each correct answer presents a complete solution. What are two possible ways to achieve this goal?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>66</char>
            <char>69</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure device groups based on operating system versions.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create and deploy device compliance policies for each platform in Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enable enhanced jailbreak detection for iOS devices.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Set up multifactor authentication (MFA) for all users.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use Microsoft Entra ID to create Conditional Access policies that require device compliance.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Creating and deploying device compliance policies for each platform in Intune (B) ensures that all devices (Windows, iOS, and Android) meet the organization's security policies, such as encryption and password protection. This action guarantees that each platform is individually managed and complies with security requirements. Using Microsoft Entra ID to create Conditional Access policies that require device compliance (E) ensures that only compliant devices, regardless of the platform, can access the corporate network. Configuring device groups based on operating system versions (A) helps organize devices but does not enforce compliance. Enabling enhanced jailbreak detection for iOS devices (C) is platform-specific and does not cover Windows or Android devices. Setting up multifactor authentication (MFA) (D) enhances security but does not address device compliance. [MD-102 3-Implement device compliance - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/implement-device-compliance/] &amp; [Step 3. Set up compliance policies for devices with Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/microsoft-365/solutions/manage-devices-with-intune-compliance-policies?view=o365-worldwide]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>51</No>
          <Text>Your company is using Microsoft Intune to manage their devices. They want to create a dynamic group that automatically includes all devices running iOS 11 or older to apply specific security policies.

You need to create a dynamic group for these devices.

Which membership rule should you use?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>device.deviceOSVersion -contains 'iOS'</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>device.deviceOSVersion -eq 'iOS 11'</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>device.deviceOSVersion -ge '11.0'</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>device.deviceOSVersion -le '11.0'</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Using device.deviceOSVersion -le '11.0' (D) is correct because it includes all devices running iOS 11 or older, which matches the requirement to apply specific security policies to those devices. device.deviceOSVersion -contains 'iOS' (A) would include all iOS devices regardless of version, which doesn’t meet the requirement. device.deviceOSVersion -eq 'iOS 11' (B) would only include devices running exactly iOS 11, excluding older versions. device.deviceOSVersion -ge '11.0' (C) includes devices running iOS 11 or newer, which is not the desired filter. [Create and manage groups in Microsoft Entra ID - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/manage-azure-active-directory-identities/4-create-manage-groups-azure-active-directory] &amp; [Manage devices joined to Microsoft Entra ID - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/administer-device-authentication/5-manage-devices-joined-azure-active-directory] &amp; [Add groups to organize users and devices - Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/fundamentals/groups-add] &amp; [MD-102 3-Implement device compliance - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/implement-device-compliance/] &amp; [Require compliant, hybrid joined devices, or MFA - Microsoft Entra ID | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/entra/identity/conditional-access/howto-conditional-access-policy-compliant-device]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>52</No>
          <Text>Your company has recently implemented Microsoft Intune to manage their fleet of Windows 10 and Windows 11 devices. They want to ensure that all devices use a strong two-factor authentication mechanism to enhance security.

You need to configure the devices to replace passwords with a more secure authentication method.

How should you configure the devices to implement this secure authentication method?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure Windows Hello for Business in the Account protection profile.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a VPN profile with two-factor authentication.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enable Credential Guard in the Endpoint protection profile.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Set up a custom OMA-URI profile for password policies.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Configuring Windows Hello for Business in the Account protection profile (A) is the correct action, as it replaces passwords with a more secure authentication method such as biometrics or PINs, enhancing security with two-factor authentication. Creating a VPN profile with two-factor authentication (B) secures remote access but does not replace passwords as the primary method of authentication. Enabling Credential Guard (C) protects against credential theft but does not replace the need for passwords. Setting up a custom OMA-URI profile for password policies (D) manages password complexity, but it does not implement a more secure, passwordless authentication method. [Execute device profiles - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/execute-device-profiles/] &amp; [Manage account protection settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/endpoint-security-account-protection-policy]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>53</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription that uses Microsoft Intune.

The following device types are enrolled in Intune:

    Windows 11

    Windows 10

    Android

    iPadOS

    iOS

You need to apply a compliance policy to all devices.

What is the minimum number of device compliance policies that you should create?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>1</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>2</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>3</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>4</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>5</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>A device compliance policy is platform specific. Windows 11 and Windows 10 compliance can be configured by using the same compliance policy. iOS and iPadOS compliance can also be monitored by using the same policy. As such, you must create compliance policies for at least three of the following: Windows 10/Windows 11, Android, and iOS/iPadOS. [MD-102 3-Implement device compliance - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/implement-device-compliance/] &amp; [Device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/device-compliance-get-started]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>54</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription that uses Microsoft Intune.

You plan to use the Require device to be marked as compliant setting in a Conditional Access policy.

You need to ensure that device compliance is evaluated.

What should you do first?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create and assign security baseline profile in Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enroll devices to Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Join devices to Microsoft Entra ID.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Register devices in Microsoft Entra ID.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Companies that have devices enrolled in Intune can use the information returned from their devices to identify specific policy compliance requirements. If devices are not enrolled in Intune, their compliance status is unavailable and cannot be evaluated by using Conditional Access policies. [MD-102 3-Implement device compliance - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/implement-device-compliance/] &amp; [Grant controls in Conditional Access policy - Microsoft Entra ID | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/entra/identity/conditional-access/concept-conditional-access-grant#require-device-to-be-marked-as-compliant]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>55</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that uses Microsoft Intune.

You create a Conditional Access Policy named Policy1.

You need to configure Policy1 to prevent users connecting to Microsoft 365 services by using non-compliant devices.

What should you configure in Policy1?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Authentication Context</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Continuous Access Evaluation</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Grant Controls</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Session Controls</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Conditional Access Grant Controls contains the option to require a device to be marked as compliant. [Require compliant, hybrid joined devices, or MFA - Microsoft Entra ID | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/entra/identity/conditional-access/howto-conditional-access-policy-compliant-device]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>56</No>
          <Text>Your company is using Microsoft Intune to manage their Windows devices. They want to implement a policy that requires all Windows devices to have a minimum OS version and to be encrypted.

How should you configure the devices to enforce these requirements?

Each correct answer is part of the solution. What three actions should you take?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>67</char>
            <char>69</char>
            <char>70</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Assign the compliance policy to a device group.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure actions for noncompliance to send email alerts.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a new device compliance policy for Windows.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enable Windows health attestation in the compliance policy.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Set the device encryption requirement in the compliance policy.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>70</Alphabet>
              <Text>Set the minimum OS version requirement in the compliance policy.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Assigning the compliance policy to a device group (A) ensures that the policy is applied to the correct set of devices. Creating a new device compliance policy for Windows (C) is essential for enforcing specific requirements, such as encryption and OS version. Setting the device encryption requirement in the compliance policy (E) ensures that all devices meet the encryption standards required by your organization. Setting the minimum OS version requirement in the compliance policy (F) ensures that devices are running at least the required version of the OS. Configuring actions for noncompliance to send email alerts (B) and enabling Windows health attestation (D) are useful features but do not directly enforce the OS version or encryption requirements. [MD-102 3-Implement device compliance - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/implement-device-compliance/] &amp; [Device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/device-compliance-get-started]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>57</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription that uses Microsoft Intune.

You have the following devices enrolled in Intune:

    Device1: Windows 11

    Device2: Android

    Device3: macOS

You plan to create an antivirus policy named AV1 in Intune.

To which devices can you apply AV1?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 and Device2 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 and Device3 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2 and Device3</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 only</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Antivirus policies in Intune can be applied to the following platforms: Windows 10 and later, macOS, Windows 11, and Windows Server. [MD-102 2-Manage Microsoft Defender for Endpoint - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/manage-defender-endpoint/] &amp; [MD-102 3-Manage Microsoft Defender in Windows client - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/manage-defender-windows-client/] &amp; [Manage antivirus settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/endpoint-security-antivirus-policy]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>58</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 100 Windows 11 devices that are enrolled to Microsoft Intune.

You need to ensure that all Intune-managed Windows 11 devices are automatically onboarded to Microsoft Defender for Endpoint.

What should you configure?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>App deployment</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Compliance policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device Configuration profile</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Security Baseline</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Once Intune is connected to Microsoft Defender for Endpoint, a Device Configuration profile can be used to onboard devices to Microsoft Defender for Endpoint. [Onboard devices and configure Microsoft Defender for Endpoint capabilities | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/microsoft-365/security/defender-endpoint/onboard-configure?view=o365-worldwide]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>59</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 100 Windows 10 devices that are enrolled to Microsoft Intune.

You deploy Intune Security Baseline profiles to all Windows 10 devices.

You notice on some devices the settings have not applied due to a conflict with existing policies.

You need to identify the conflicting policy. The solution must minimize administrative effort.

What should you do?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>View the Assignment Failures report in the Microsoft Defender Portal.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>View the Assignment Failures report in the Microsoft Intune Admin Center.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>View the Noncompliant Devices report in the Microsoft Defender Portal.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>View the Noncompliant Devices report in the Microsoft Intune Admin Center.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>The Assignment Failures report contains failure and conflict information for Configuration profiles. [Microsoft Intune reports - Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/fundamentals/reports]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>60</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 100 Windows 11 devices that are enrolled to Microsoft Intune.

You need to ensure that malware quarantined by Microsoft Defender is retained for 14 days and then deleted.

What should you do?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Modify the Anti-Malware policies from the Microsoft Defender Portal.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Modify the Anti-Malware policies from the Microsoft Intune Admin Center.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Modify the Endpoint Security Antivirus policy from the Microsoft Intune Admin Center.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Modify the Endpoint Security Antivirus policy from the Microsoft Defender Portal.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>The Endpoint Security Antivirus policy controls the behavior for quarantine retention in Microsoft Defender. [Windows Antivirus policy settings for Microsoft Defender Antivirus for Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/antivirus-microsoft-defender-settings-windows]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>61</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription that includes 500 Windows 11 devices that are managed by using Microsoft Intune.

You need to apply granular security controls to the Microsoft Edge configuration on each device. The solution must minimize administrative efforts.

What should you configure?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>a Compliance policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text> a Security Baseline </Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Attack surface reduction</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Endpoint detection and response</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>You need to configure a Security Baseline in order to apply the security controls to the Microsoft Edge configuration of each device. [Learn about Windows security baselines you can deploy with Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/security-baselines]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>62</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 500 Windows 11 Enterprise devices that are managed by using Microsoft Intune and Endpoint Security.

You need to ensure that users are automatically added to the local RDP users group. The solution must follow the principle of least privilege.

What should you configure?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>a Dynamic Group</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Account protection</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device Compliance</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Endpoint detection and response</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>With the Account Protection option, you can easily assign a Microsoft Entra ID group (or user) to be part of the local device group with RDP users. [Manage account protection settings with endpoint security policies in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/endpoint-security-account-protection-policy]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>63</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription.

You plan to deploy and enroll the following devices into Microsoft Intune:

    Device1: Windows 11

    Device2: Windows 10

    Device3: Android

    Device4: iOS

You configure an enrollment status page (ESP) named Enrollment1.

On which devices can Enrollment1 be displayed during device provisioning?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 and Device2 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2, and Device3 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2, and Device4 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2, Device3, and Device4 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 only</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>The ESP displays the provisioning status to users enrolling Windows devices and signing in for the first time. You can configure the ESP to block device use until all required policies and applications are installed. As such, the ESP can be displayed on Windows 11 and Windows 10 devices only. [MD-102 1-Deploy Devices using Windows Autopilot - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-devices-windows-autopilot/] &amp; [Set up the Enrollment Status Page in the admin center - Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/enrollment/windows-enrollment-status]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>64</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that uses Windows Autopilot and includes a device named Device1.

You need to trigger a Windows Autopilot reset on Device1.

What will be retained once the reset has completed?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>modified Windows settings</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>personal user files</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>egion, language, and keyboard settings</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Wi-Fi connection details</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Wi-Fi connection details are retained after an autopilot reset. Personal user files are removed during an Autopilot reset and region, language, keyboard, and modified Windows settings are reset to default during an Autopilot reset. [Windows Autopilot Reset | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/autopilot/windows-autopilot-reset]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>65</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that contains the following devices:

    Device1: Windows 10 20H2, TPM 1.1

    Device2: Windows 10 21H2, TPM 2.0

    Device3: Windows 10 22H2, TPM 2.0

You need to use Windows Autopilot for pre-provisioned deployment.

Which devices meet the requirements for pre-provisioned deployment?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2 and Device3</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device2 and Device3 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device2 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device3 only</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Device2 and Device3 meet the minimum requirements for OS (1903) and TPM (2.0) for Windows Autopilot for pre-provisioned deployment. [Windows Autopilot for pre-provisioned deployment | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/autopilot/pre-provision]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>66</No>
          <Text>Your company is planning to upgrade its fleet of Windows 10 devices to Windows 11. The IT department has identified that some devices do not meet the minimum hardware requirements for Windows 11.

How should you ensure that only eligible devices are upgraded to Windows 11 while minimizing administrative overhead?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deploy a custom script to gather hardware information from each device.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Manually check each device's hardware specifications against Windows 11 requirements.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use Endpoint Analytics to generate a Windows 11 hardware readiness report.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use the PC Health Check app on each device.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Using Endpoint Analytics to generate a Windows 11 hardware readiness report (C) is correct because this tool allows you to automatically assess the hardware compatibility of your entire fleet of devices, minimizing administrative overhead. It provides an efficient and scalable way to determine which devices meet the Windows 11 upgrade requirements. Deploying a custom script to gather hardware information from each device (A) is incorrect because it adds complexity and requires more manual management than necessary. Manually checking each device's hardware specifications (B) is also incorrect because it is time-consuming and inefficient, especially for a large number of devices. Using the PC Health Check app on each device (D) is incorrect as it would require manual execution on every device, which increases administrative overhead. [Explore readiness tools - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deployment-readiness/3-explore-readiness-tools] &amp; [Use Autopilot for modern deployment - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-devices-windows-autopilot/2-use-autopilot-for-modern-deployment] &amp; [Plan for Windows 11 | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/windows/whats-new/windows-11-plan]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>67</No>
          <Text>You are building a Windows Autopilot solution.

During testing you notice that deployments are failing due to users restarting devices before the deployment has finished.

You need to provide users with the option of collecting logs during deployment and contact details for the help.

What should you modify?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>configuration policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>deployment profile</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>device group settings</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enrollment status page</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>By default, the Enrollment status page does not show users the progress of enrollment. Based on the input the result could be a timeout (it takes long time). Configuring an Enrollment status page allows the user to view additional details on the progress and provide you with insights into what is happening. [First-run experience with Autopilot and the Enrollment Status Page | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/managed-desktop/deploy/esp-first-run?source=recommendations]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>68</No>
          <Text>Your company is planning to deploy Windows 11 to a large number of new devices purchased from an OEM. The devices come with Windows 11 Pro pre-installed, but Contoso needs them configured with specific organizational settings and applications.

How should you streamline the deployment process to ensure minimal IT intervention while meeting Contoso's configuration requirements?

Each correct answer presents part of the solution. What two actions should you perform?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>68</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a provisioning package using Windows Imaging and Configuration Designer (ICD).</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deploy a custom Windows 11 image using Windows Deployment Services (WDS).</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Perform an in-place upgrade from Windows 11 Pro to Windows 11 Enterprise.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use Windows Autopilot to customize the Out-of-Box Experience (OOBE).</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Creating a provisioning package using Windows Imaging and Configuration Designer (ICD) (A) is correct because ICD allows you to apply custom settings, configurations, and applications during device setup, streamlining the process and minimizing IT intervention. This is particularly useful for new devices that already have Windows 11 Pro pre-installed. Using Windows Autopilot to customize the Out-of-Box Experience (OOBE) (D) is also correct because Autopilot automates the configuration process, ensuring that devices are set up with specific organizational settings and applications while requiring minimal user interaction. Deploying a custom Windows 11 image using Windows Deployment Services (WDS) (B) is incorrect because it requires more manual effort and infrastructure, which contradicts the goal of minimal IT intervention. Performing an in-place upgrade from Windows 11 Pro to Windows 11 Enterprise (C) is incorrect because an upgrade is not necessary in this case; instead, you can use existing tools to manage configurations without needing to change the operating system version. [Use Autopilot for modern deployment - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-devices-windows-autopilot/2-use-autopilot-for-modern-deployment] &amp; [Evaluate upgrades and migrations in modern transitioning - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/plan-transition-modern-endpoint-management/5-evaluate-upgrades-migrations-modern-transitioning] &amp; [Windows deployment scenarios | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/windows/deployment/windows-deployment-scenarios]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>69</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes the following devices:

    Device1: Windows 10 Home

    Device2: Windows 11 Professional

    Device3: Windows 8.1 Enterprise

    Device4: Android 9.0

You need to identify which devices support Intune configuration policies.

Which devices should you identify?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device2 and Device3 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device2, Device3, and Device4 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device3 and Device4 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2, Device3, and Device4</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Device1, Device2, Device3 and Device4 can all be managed using Microsoft Intune. The minimum Windows version is Windows 8.1, the minimum Windows edition is Home and the minimum Android version is 8.0. [Operating systems and browsers supported by Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/fundamentals/supported-devices-browsers]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>70</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 100 Windows 10 devices that are enrolled to Microsoft Intune.

You need to deploy Microsoft 365 Apps for Business to all devices. The solution must ensure that Microsoft Visio is included in the deployment.

What should you do first?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Assign a Visio license to your admin account.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a device configuration from the Microsoft 365 Apps admin center.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a device configuration profile from the Microsoft Intune admin center.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a new app configuration policy from the Microsoft Intune admin center.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>A device configuration in the Microsoft 365 Apps Admin Center allows for the customization of the Microsoft 365 Apps installation, including Visio and/or Project. [Overview of the Microsoft 365 Apps admin center - Deploy Office | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/deployoffice/admincenter/overview]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>71</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription.

Users connect to Microsoft 365 services by using their personal iOS and Android devices. The devices are NOT managed by Intune.

You need to prevent Microsoft 365 files being saved locally to non-managed devices.

What should you use?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>App Configuration policies</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>App deployment</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>App Protection policies</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configuration profiles</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>App Protection policies can secure apps on unmanaged devices, including preventing files from being saved locally. [Create and assign an app protection policy - Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/quickstart-create-assign-app-policy]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>72</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 100 users. Users access Microsoft 365 services by using Microsoft Edge on personal Android devices.

You need to deploy Microsoft Edge bookmarks to the Android devices.

What should you configure?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>a Compliance policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>a Configuration profile</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>an App Configuration policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>an App Protection policy</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>An App Configuration policy allows for app settings to be configured regardless of the device's enrollment state or how the app is delivered to the device. [App configuration policies for Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/app-configuration-policies-overview]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>73</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes iOS and Android devices that are managed by using Microsoft Intune.

You plan to implement a data protection framework for financial data.

You need to create app protection policies for the framework to protect company data in the event that a device is rooted or jailbroken.

What two actions should the policy perform? Each correct answer presents part of the solution.</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>66</char>
            <char>68</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Block access.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Encrypt organizational data.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Reset the PIN.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Wipe data.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>The finance department has access to financial data that poses a uniquely high risk. Any change into devices that become jailbroken or rooted should immediately result in a wipe to ensure no data can be retrieved. All organization data should be encrypted on the device by default. [Data protection framework using app protection policies - Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/app-protection-framework]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>74</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription. The subscription contains a user named User1 and a Microsoft Entra joined device named Device1 that runs Windows 11 Pro.

You need to implement subscription activation for Device1.

What should you do?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Assign a license to User1.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure Windows Autopilot and create a deployment profile.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enroll Device1 to Microsoft Intune and assign a compliance policy.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enroll Device1 to Microsoft Intune and assign a device configuration profile.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Subscription activation is performed by assigning a user a Windows 10/11 Enterprise license. When a user signs in to a Windows Pro device, the device is automatically and transparently activated and upgraded to the Enterprise edition. [MD-102 2-Implement dynamic deployment methods - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/implement-dynamic-deployment/] &amp; [Windows subscription activation - Windows Deployment | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/windows/deployment/windows-10-subscription-activation]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>75</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E3 subscription that includes 500 devices and uses Microsoft Intune. The devices run Windows 10 22H2 and are configured with Windows Recovery Environment.

You need to deploy Windows Autopilot. The solution must minimize the time taken to revert devices to a business-ready state.

What should you do first?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a deployment profile.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a dynamic device group.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enable the DisableAutomaticReDeploymentCredentials policy.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Manually register the devices with Windows Autopilot.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>The first step is to create a deployment profile that converts all targeted devices to Autopilot devices. [Windows Autopilot Reset | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/autopilot/windows-autopilot-reset] &amp; [Configure Autopilot profiles | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/autopilot/profiles]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>76</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that uses Microsoft Intune.

You create a Windows Autopilot deployment profile named Profile1.

You need to ensure that devices are automatically joined to Microsoft Entra ID as part of the deployment. The solution must ensure that users can only sign into the device using their Microsoft 365 account.

What setting should you configure?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deployment mode</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Hide change account options</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Join to Microsoft Entra as</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>User account type</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Hiding the change account options will prevent new devices from displaying on the company sign-in and domain error pages. [Configure Autopilot profiles | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/autopilot/profiles]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>77</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription.

You need to ensure that any Intune managed Windows 10 Device that has been inactive for 180 days is automatically wiped and that the enrollment is deleted from Microsoft Intune.

What should you configure?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Compliance policies</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configuration profiles</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device Cleanup rules</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Security Baselines</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Device Cleanup rules can be configured to automatically delete and wipe any device that has been inactive for a configured period of time between 30 and 270 days. Compliance policies measure the compliance of a device against configured criteria and can mark a device as non-compliant and Configuration profiles allow settings to be deployed to Intune enrolled devices, but neither will automatically delete and wipe a device. Security Baselines are Configuration profiles apply best practice security configurations to devices. [Retire or wipe devices using Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/remote-actions/devices-wipe]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>78</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription and 50 iOS devices.

You plan to implement Defender for Endpoint for all corporate iOS devices.

You need to onboard the iOS devices to Defender for Endpoint.

What tool should you use?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Group policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>JAMF Pro</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>local scripts</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Microsoft Intune</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Only Intune allows you to deploy the Microsoft Defender Endpoint app for iOS devices. Group policies, local scripts, and JAMF Pro are not allowed on an iOS device. [Onboard devices and configure Microsoft Defender for Endpoint capabilities | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/microsoft-365/security/defender-endpoint/onboard-configure?view=o365-worldwide]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>79</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 500 Android tablets that are managed by using Microsoft Intune.

You need to ensure that updates are automatically deployed to the tablets.

What should you configure?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>a custom configuration profile</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>a device restrictions configuration profile</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Update policies for Android</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Update rings for Android</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Only the Device restrictions policy for organization allows you to set these settings which can be configured using a device restriction configuration profile. [Corporate-owned Android Enterprise device restriction settings in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/configuration/device-restrictions-android-for-work]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>80</No>
          <Text>Your company has a diverse range of devices, including both company-owned and BYOD (Bring Your Own Device), that need to access Microsoft 365 services. The IT department wants to ensure that sensitive company data is protected on all devices, regardless of whether they are managed by Intune.

How should you create app protection policies to apply different levels of data loss prevention (DLP) controls based on whether the device is managed by Intune or not?

Each correct answer presents part of the solution. What two actions should you perform?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>66</char>
            <char>68</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure device compliance policies instead of app protection policies.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a separate app protection policy for Intune managed devices with relaxed DLP controls.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a single app protection policy and apply it to all devices.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create one app protection policy for unmanaged devices with strict DLP controls.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use conditional access policies to enforce DLP controls.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Creating a separate app protection policy for Intune-managed devices with relaxed DLP controls (B) is correct because managed devices are already secured, allowing for more flexible policies. Creating one app protection policy for unmanaged devices with strict DLP controls (D) is correct because unmanaged devices pose a higher risk, so stricter policies help protect sensitive data. Configuring device compliance policies (A) is incorrect because compliance policies focus on device health, not app-specific data protection. Using a single policy for all devices (C) is incorrect because it doesn’t differentiate between managed and unmanaged devices. Conditional access (E) is incorrect because it controls access but doesn’t apply specific DLP controls within apps. [Deploy applications with Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-applications/2-deploy-applications-intune] &amp; [Implement mobile application management policies in Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/execute-mobile-application-management/5-implement-mobile-application-management-policies-intune] &amp; [Policies for Office apps - Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/app-office-policies]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>81</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 100 Android devices that are enrolled to Microsoft Intune.

You plan to deploy an Android app to all managed Android devices by using Microsoft Intune.

You create a new app deployment and enter the name and details of the app.

What should you do next?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enter the AppStore URL for the app.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enter the publishers download URL for the app.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Upload the APK for the app to Azure storage.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Upload the APK for the app to the Microsoft Intune admin center.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>The AppStore URL is required during the app deployment and allows the app to be located and installed on devices. Uploading the APK for the app is not required to deploy an Android application and the publisher URL is not required, this must be a link to the public Play Store URL. [Add Android store apps to Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/store-apps-android]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>82</No>
          <Text>Your company is implementing a new email application for its employees. The IT department wants to ensure that the application is configured to block external images and restrict certain URLs for security reasons. Employees use a mix of iOS and Android devices, both managed and unmanaged.

What two actions should you perform to apply these configurations to the email application across all devices?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>66</char>
            <char>67</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a separate app protection policy for each device type.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create an app configuration policy for managed apps and include the required settings.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create an app configuration policy for managed devices and include the required settings.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Instruct employees to manually configure the email application settings.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Creating an app configuration policy for managed apps (B) is correct because it allows you to enforce settings, such as blocking external images and restricting certain URLs, across all managed devices consistently. Creating an app configuration policy for managed devices (C) is also correct as it ensures that the required security configurations are applied to those devices, maintaining compliance. Creating separate app protection policies for each device type (A) is incorrect because it does not specifically address the requirements for blocking images and URLs. Instructing employees to manually configure the email application settings (D) is inefficient and could lead to inconsistent application of security policies. [Deploy applications with Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-applications/2-deploy-applications-intune] &amp; [Implement mobile application management policies in Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/execute-mobile-application-management/5-implement-mobile-application-management-policies-intune] &amp; [App configuration policies for Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/app-configuration-policies-overview]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>83</No>
          <Text>Your company is moving to a cloud-first infrastructure and needs to ensure that all devices accessing its resources comply with security policies. These devices include a mix of company-owned and personal devices across Windows, iOS, and Android platforms.

You need to implement a solution that allows both types of devices to access organizational resources while ensuring they meet security compliance.

Each correct answer presents part of the solution. Which three actions should you perform?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>66</char>
            <char>67</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Apply Conditional Access policies to enforce compliance.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enroll devices in Microsoft Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Register user-owned devices to Microsoft Entra ID.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Require all devices to use a Microsoft account for sign-in.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use Group Policy Objects (GPOs) to manage device compliance.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Registering user-owned devices to Microsoft Entra ID allows the organization to recognize and manage these devices. Enrolling devices in Microsoft Intune ensures that they can be managed and meet security compliance requirements. Applying Conditional Access policies enforces compliance before allowing access to organizational resources. Requiring all devices to use a Microsoft account for sign-in is unnecessary, and using Group Policy Objects (GPOs) is not relevant for managing compliance in a cloud-first infrastructure. [Use Microsoft Entra join with automatic MDM enrollment - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/implement-dynamic-deployment/5-use-azure-ad-join-automatic-mobile-device-management-enrollment] &amp; [Examine Microsoft Entra join prerequisites limitations and benefits - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/administer-device-authentication/3-examine-azure-active-directory-join-prerequisites-limitations-benefits] &amp; [What are Microsoft Entra registered devices? - Microsoft Entra ID | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/entra/identity/devices/concept-device-registration]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>84</No>
          <Text>Your company is preparing to deploy a large number of Android devices for field agents. These devices must be centrally managed and restricted to access only specific work-related applications. The devices will not be used for personal purposes.

What steps should you take to configure the enrollment settings for these Android devices to ensure they are fully managed and restricted to work-related use?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure an Android device administrator enrollment profile.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure an Android Enterprise dedicated device enrollment profile.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure an Android Enterprise fully managed enrollment profile.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure an Android Enterprise work profile enrollment profile.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Configuring an Android Enterprise fully managed enrollment profile (C) ensures that the devices are fully managed by Intune and restricted to work-related use. An Android Enterprise work profile (D) is more appropriate for BYOD scenarios, while an Android Enterprise dedicated device profile (B) is intended for single-use devices, such as kiosks. An Android device administrator profile (A) does not provide the same level of management and control, making it unsuitable for this scenario. [Enroll devices using Microsoft Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/enroll-devices-use-intune/] &amp; [Step 5 – Enroll devices in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enroll?tabs=work-profile%2Ccorporate-owned-apple%2Cautomatic-enrollment]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>85</No>
          <Text>Your company wants to implement Conditional Access policies to protect organizational data. They need to ensure that only devices compliant with their Intune policies can access Microsoft 365 services.

How should you configure the devices to implement these Conditional Access policies?

Each correct answer is part of the solution. What three actions should you take?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>67</char>
            <char>69</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Assign the Conditional Access policy to the user group accessing Microsoft 365 services.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure the policy to allow access from unmanaged devices.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a Conditional Access policy in Microsoft Entra ID.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enable location-based access control in the Conditional Access policy.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Set the policy to require device compliance from Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Assigning the Conditional Access policy to the user group accessing Microsoft 365 services (A) ensures that the policy applies specifically to the users who need access, enforcing compliance for that group. Creating a Conditional Access policy in Microsoft Entra ID (C) is necessary to define and enforce access rules based on device compliance. Setting the policy to require device compliance from Intune (E) ensures that only compliant devices are allowed access to Microsoft 365 services. Configuring the policy to allow access from unmanaged devices (B) contradicts the goal of ensuring only compliant devices can access services, and enabling location-based access control (D) manages access based on location but does not enforce compliance with Intune policies. [MD-102 3-Implement device compliance - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/implement-device-compliance/] &amp; [Windows compliance settings in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/compliance-policy-create-windows]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>86</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription.

You need to enforce Intune compliance for the following device types:

    iPad

    iPhone

    Windows 11

    Windows 10

    Android

What is the minimum number of Compliance policies required?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>1</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>3</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>4</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>5</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Three is correct. At a minimum, Android Enterprise, iOS/iPadOS, and Windows 10 and later Compliance policies are required. [Device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/device-compliance-get-started]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>87</No>
          <Text>Your company has implemented Microsoft Intune to manage devices, but some devices are accessing corporate resources without being compliant with the company's security policies.

How should you configure the devices to ensure that only compliant devices can access corporate resources?

Each correct answer is part of the solution. What three actions should you take?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>66</char>
            <char>70</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure Conditional Access policies to require device compliance.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create and assign device compliance policies to user groups.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deploy a device configuration policy to enforce encryption.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enable Enhanced jailbreak detection for iOS devices.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Set the 'Compliance status validity period' to 60 days.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>70</Alphabet>
              <Text>Set the 'Mark devices with no compliance policy assigned as' setting to 'Not compliant'.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Configuring Conditional Access policies to require device compliance (A) ensures that only devices meeting your organization's compliance policies can access corporate resources. Creating and assigning device compliance policies to user groups (B) defines the compliance requirements, such as security settings, that devices must adhere to. Setting the 'Mark devices with no compliance policy assigned as' setting to 'Not compliant' (F) ensures that any devices without a compliance policy are treated as non-compliant and restricted from accessing resources. Deploying a device configuration policy to enforce encryption (C) focuses on configuring specific device settings but does not directly manage access. Enabling Enhanced jailbreak detection (D) is limited to iOS devices, and setting the 'Compliance status validity period' (E) affects how long devices remain compliant but does not actively enforce compliance. [MD-102 3-Implement device compliance - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/implement-device-compliance/] &amp; [Device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/device-compliance-get-started]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>88</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 500 Windows 11 devices that are managed by using Microsoft Intune.

Your company uses Intune to manage devices and has configured compliance policies and conditional access policies. Several users complain they cannot access company resources.

You must identify potential problems for all users. The solution must require minimal administrative effort.

Which two services can you use to get an overview of potential problems? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>69</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Review the Device compliance report.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Review the Device configuration report.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Review the sign-in logs.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use the troubleshoot + support.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>View the details of the created policy.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>The details of a policy provide a diagram overview and the device compliance report provides details for all devices. [Monitor results of your device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/compliance-policy-monitor]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>89</No>
          <Text>Your company has a diverse range of devices, including both company-owned and BYOD (Bring Your Own Device), that need to access Microsoft 365 services. The IT department wants to ensure that sensitive company data is protected on all devices, regardless of whether they are managed by Intune.

How should you create app protection policies to apply different levels of data loss prevention (DLP) controls based on whether the device is managed by Intune or not?

Each correct answer presents part of the solution. What two actions should you perform?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>66</char>
            <char>68</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure device compliance policies instead of app protection policies.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a separate app protection policy for Intune managed devices with relaxed DLP controls.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a single app protection policy and apply it to all devices.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create one app protection policy for unmanaged devices with strict DLP controls.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use conditional access policies to enforce DLP controls.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Creating a separate app protection policy for Intune-managed devices with relaxed DLP controls (B) is correct because managed devices are already secured, allowing for more flexible policies. Creating one app protection policy for unmanaged devices with strict DLP controls (D) is correct because unmanaged devices pose a higher risk, so stricter policies help protect sensitive data. Configuring device compliance policies (A) is incorrect because compliance policies focus on device health, not app-specific data protection. Using a single policy for all devices (C) is incorrect because it doesn’t differentiate between managed and unmanaged devices. Conditional access (E) is incorrect because it controls access but doesn’t apply specific DLP controls within apps. [Deploy applications with Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-applications/2-deploy-applications-intune] &amp; [Implement mobile application management policies in Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/execute-mobile-application-management/5-implement-mobile-application-management-policies-intune] &amp; [Policies for Office apps - Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/app-office-policies]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>90</No>
          <Text>Your company is implementing a BYOD policy for employees using Android devices. They need to ensure that work and personal data remain separate on these devices.

You need to configure the appropriate enrollment profile for these Android devices.

Which enrollment profile should you configure?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>66</char>
            <char>67</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Android Enterprise dedicated</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Android Enterprise fully managed</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Android Enterprise work profile</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device Enrollment Manager (DEM)</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>The Android Enterprise work profile (C) is designed to keep work and personal data separate on BYOD devices. The fully managed (B) and dedicated (A) profiles are intended for corporate-owned devices, and the Device Enrollment Manager (DEM) (D) is used for enrolling large numbers of devices by an administrator, making it unsuitable for a BYOD scenario.
[Enroll devices using Microsoft Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/enroll-devices-use-intune/] &amp; [Set up automatic enrollment in Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/enrollment/quickstart-setup-auto-enrollment]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>91</No>
          <Text>You manage a network that contains the following devices:

    Device1, Windows 11 Enterprise

    Device2, Windows 11 Pro

    Device3, Windows 11 for Education

    Device4, Windows 11 Home

Which devices can be added to an Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS) domain?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 and Device2 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2, and Device3 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2, Device3, and Device4</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Device1, Device2, and Device3 is correct. Windows 11 Enterprise, Windows 11 Pro and Windows 11 for Education are all supported for Active Directory domain Join. Windows 11 Home is not.

Device1 only is incorrect. Windows 11 Enterprise, Windows 11 Pro and Windows 11 for Education are all supported for Active Directory domain Join. Windows 11 Home is not.

Device1 and Device2 is incorrect. Windows 11 Enterprise, Windows 11 Pro and Windows 11 for Education are all supported for Active Directory domain Join. Windows 11 Home is not.

Device1, Device2, Device3, and Device4 is incorrect. Windows 11 Enterprise, Windows 11 Pro and Windows 11 for Education are all supported for Active Directory domain Join. Windows 11 Home is not.
[Examine Windows client editions and requirements - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/examine-windows-client-editions-requirements/]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>92</No>
          <Text>You have an on-premises network and a hybrid Microsoft 365 that uses Microsoft Entra Connect.

You need to identify the devices that will be visible by using the Microsoft Entra admin center.

What should you identify?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Microsoft Entra joined devices only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Microsoft Entra hybrid joined devices and Active Directory Domain joined devices only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Microsoft Entra joined devices, Microsoft Entra hybrid joined devices, and Microsoft Entra registered Devices only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Active Directory Domain joined devices, Microsoft Entra joined devices, Microsoft Entra hybrid joined devices, and Microsoft Entra registered devices</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Active Directory joined devices are not present in the Microsoft Entra admin center.

Microsoft Entra joined devices, Microsoft Entra Hybrid joined devices, and Microsoft Entra registered devices are present and viewable from the Microsoft Entra admin center.
[What is device identity in Microsoft Entra ID? - Microsoft Entra ID | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/entra/identity/devices/overview]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>93</No>
          <Text>Your company needs to enroll a large number of iOS devices for their sales team. These devices are company-owned and need to be managed with minimal user interaction. The company also wants the devices to be enrolled in supervised mode and shipped directly to users.

You need to configure the enrollment settings for these iOS devices.

Which two actions should you perform?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>67</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create an enrollment profile in the Intune admin center.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Instruct users to manually install the Company Portal app from the App Store.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use Apple Business Manager to configure Automated Device Enrollment (ADE).</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use Apple Configurator to enroll the devices.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Using Apple Business Manager to configure Automated Device Enrollment (ADE) (C) allows for bulk enrollment of company-owned devices in supervised mode with minimal user interaction. Creating an enrollment profile in the Intune admin center (A) ensures that the devices receive the necessary configurations automatically. Manually installing the Company Portal app (B) and using Apple Configurator (D) are less efficient and involve more manual steps, making them unsuitable for this large-scale deployment scenario.
[Enroll devices using Microsoft Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/enroll-devices-use-intune/] &amp; [iOS/iPadOS device enrollment guide for Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/fundamentals/deployment-guide-enrollment-ios-ipados]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>94</No>
          <Text>Your company has implemented Microsoft Intune to manage devices, but some devices are accessing corporate resources without being compliant with the company's security policies.

How should you configure the devices to ensure that only compliant devices can access corporate resources?

Each correct answer is part of the solution. What three actions should you take?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>66</char>
            <char>70</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure Conditional Access policies to require device compliance.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create and assign device compliance policies to user groups.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deploy a device configuration policy to enforce encryption.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enable Enhanced jailbreak detection for iOS devices.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Set the 'Compliance status validity period' to 60 days.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>70</Alphabet>
              <Text>Set the 'Mark devices with no compliance policy assigned as' setting to 'Not compliant'.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Configuring Conditional Access policies to require device compliance (A) ensures that only devices meeting your organization's compliance policies can access corporate resources. Creating and assigning device compliance policies to user groups (B) defines the compliance requirements, such as security settings, that devices must adhere to. Setting the 'Mark devices with no compliance policy assigned as' setting to 'Not compliant' (F) ensures that any devices without a compliance policy are treated as non-compliant and restricted from accessing resources. Deploying a device configuration policy to enforce encryption (C) focuses on configuring specific device settings but does not directly manage access. Enabling Enhanced jailbreak detection (D) is limited to iOS devices, and setting the 'Compliance status validity period' (E) affects how long devices remain compliant but does not actively enforce compliance.
[MD-102 3-Implement device compliance - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/implement-device-compliance/] &amp; [Device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/device-compliance-get-started]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>95</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 500 Windows 11 devices that are managed by using Microsoft Intune.

You create a new Compliance policy notification to alert device owners when their devices become non-compliant.

How will users be notified if their device becomes non-compliant?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>email</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>phone toast notification</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>SMS</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Windows notification</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Users will be notified using email notifications as they are the only option supported by Microsoft Intune. SMS, Windows notifications, and phone toast notifications are not supported by Microsoft Intune.
[Send notifications to noncompliant devices - Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/quickstart-send-notification]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>96</No>
          <Text>Your company is planning to deploy Windows 11 to its fleet of 500 devices. They want to ensure that the deployment process is streamlined and that all devices are configured uniformly. The fleet includes both new and existing devices, and the company aims to minimize manual intervention during the deployment process.

How should you approach the deployment to ensure uniform configuration and minimal manual effort?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deploy Windows upgrade with Microsoft Configuration Manager.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Implement Windows client deployment by using Windows Autopilot.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Perform an in-place upgrade on each device manually.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use provisioning packages for all devices.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Implementing Windows client deployment by using Windows Autopilot (B) is correct because Autopilot automates the deployment process, minimizing manual intervention and ensuring uniform configuration across both new and existing devices. It is ideal for large-scale deployments where consistency and automation are key. Deploying Windows upgrades with Microsoft Configuration Manager (A) is incorrect because although it’s powerful for managing deployments, the question focuses on Autopilot. Performing an in-place upgrade manually (C) is inefficient and labor-intensive, making it unsuitable for a large fleet of 500 devices. Using provisioning packages for all devices (D) is incorrect because provisioning packages are typically used for smaller-scale, specific configurations and are not ideal for full OS deployments.
[Additional Microsoft 365 Apps Deployment Tools - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/administer-endpoint-applications/5-additional-microsoft-365-apps-deployment-tools] &amp; [Explore Windows 365 - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/manage-windows-365/2-explore-windows-365] &amp; [Deploy Windows with Microsoft 365 | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/windows/deployment/deploy-m365]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>97</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription that uses Microsoft Intune.

You have the following devices enrolled in Intune:

    Device1: Windows 11

    Device2: macOS

    Device3: iPadOS

You plan to use a template to create an Endpoint Protection device configuration profile in Intune.

For which devices can you create an Endpoint Protection device configuration profile template?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 and Device2 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 and Device3 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2, and Device3</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 only</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>The Endpoint Protection device configuration template is available only for Windows 10 and later and macOS platforms. This profile is unavailable for iPadOS platform.
[Execute device profiles - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/execute-device-profiles/] &amp; [Create device profiles in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/configuration/device-profile-create]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>98</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription that uses Microsoft Intune.

Users enroll Windows 11 devices in Intune.

You need to configure an update schedule during which Windows updates are installed on the enrolled devices.

What should you configure in Intune?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>compliance policy</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>feature updates for Windows 10 and later</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>quality updates for Windows 10 and later</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>update ring for Windows 10 and later</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Update rings specify how and when Windows as a Service updates Windows 10/11 devices with feature and quality updates. An update ring includes the User experience settings, in which you can configure the automatic update features (including auto install and restart at maintenance time), active hours start, and active hours end.
[Configure Update rings for Windows 10 and later policy in Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/windows-10-update-rings]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>99</No>
          <Text>Your company has a diverse range of devices, including both company-owned and BYOD (Bring Your Own Device), that need to access Microsoft 365 services. The IT department wants to ensure that sensitive company data is protected on all devices, regardless of whether they are managed by Intune.

How should you create app protection policies to apply different levels of data loss prevention (DLP) controls based on whether the device is managed by Intune or not?

Each correct answer presents part of the solution. What two actions should you perform?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>66</char>
            <char>68</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure device compliance policies instead of app protection policies.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a separate app protection policy for Intune managed devices with relaxed DLP controls.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a single app protection policy and apply it to all devices.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create one app protection policy for unmanaged devices with strict DLP controls.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use conditional access policies to enforce DLP controls.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Creating a separate app protection policy for Intune-managed devices with relaxed DLP controls (B) is correct because managed devices are already secured, allowing for more flexible policies. Creating one app protection policy for unmanaged devices with strict DLP controls (D) is correct because unmanaged devices pose a higher risk, so stricter policies help protect sensitive data. Configuring device compliance policies (A) is incorrect because compliance policies focus on device health, not app-specific data protection. Using a single policy for all devices (C) is incorrect because it doesn’t differentiate between managed and unmanaged devices. Conditional access (E) is incorrect because it controls access but doesn’t apply specific DLP controls within apps.
[Deploy applications with Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-applications/2-deploy-applications-intune] &amp; [Implement mobile application management policies in Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/execute-mobile-application-management/5-implement-mobile-application-management-policies-intune] &amp; [Policies for Office apps - Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/app-office-policies]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>100</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes a group named Group1 that contains 500 Android devices.

You provision a new App Protection policy in Microsoft Intune with the following settings:

    Target to apps on all device types: Yes

    Target Policy to: All Microsoft Apps

    Save copies of org data: Block

    Allow user to save copies to selected services: OneDrive for Business

    Assignments: Group1

Users report that they can save data to their devices.

You need to ensure that users are prevented from saving data to their local devices.

Which setting should you modify?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Allow user to save copies to selected services</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Assignments</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Save copies of org data</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Target Policy to</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>The Assignments setting needs to be modified to include either All devices or All users. Assigning the policy to a security group containing devices will not capture new devices or devices that are not registered in Microsoft Entra ID.
[Create and deploy app protection policies - Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/apps/app-protection-policies]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>101</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription.

You purchase 100 Windows devices that will be deployed to new users.

You need to ensure that you can deploy the devices by manually registering the devices using Windows Autopilot.

What should you do first?</Text>
          <Answer>66</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Upload the device name of each device to Microsoft Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Upload the hardware ID of each device to Microsoft Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Upload the IP address of each device to Microsoft Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Upload the MAC address of each device to Microsoft Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Windows Autopilot requires the hardware ID of each machine to be uploaded before the machine can be used with Autopilot. The MAC address, device name, and IP address is not needed for Windows Autopilot.
[Manually register devices with Windows Autopilot | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/autopilot/add-devices]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>102</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that uses Microsoft Intune.

You create a Windows Autopilot deployment profile named Profile1.

You need to manually register a device to test Profile1.

What information can you use to register the device?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Hardware Hash</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>MAC Address</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>PKID</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>tuple</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>To register a new device in Microsoft Intune you must capture the Hardware Hash
The MAC address, as a unique identifier, is not required to capture the hardware hash if you can sign into the device and can use PowerShell. The PKID (Windows product ID) and tuple are not valid options to register a new device to Microsoft Intune or a profile.
[Manually register devices with Windows Autopilot | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/autopilot/add-devices] &amp; [Configure Autopilot profiles | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/autopilot/profiles]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>103</No>
          <Text>You want to ensure that all new Windows 11 devices are joined to Microsoft Entra ID during the out-of-box experience (OOBE). The IT department has configured the device registration service and ensured that all necessary prerequisites are met.

You need to join the new Windows 11 devices to Microsoft Entra ID during the OOBE.

Each correct answer presents part of the solution. Which three actions should you perform?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>66</char>
            <char>69</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Provide the credentials that your organization provided.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Select 'Set up for work or school' when prompted.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Select 'This device belongs to my family' when prompted.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Skip the network connection step during setup.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Turn on the new device and start the setup process.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Turning on the device and starting the setup process (A) is the first step. Selecting 'Set up for work or school' (B) ensures the device is prepared for Microsoft Entra ID join. Providing the organization's credentials (C) completes the authentication process. Selecting 'This device belongs to my family' (D) is incorrect as it does not align with the goal. Skipping the network connection step (E) is incorrect because the device must be connected to the Internet to complete the Microsoft Entra join.
[Manage device authentication - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/administer-device-authentication/] &amp; [Join a new Windows 11 device with Microsoft Entra ID during the out of box experience - Microsoft Entra ID | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/entra/identity/devices/device-join-out-of-box]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>104</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes a user named User1.

You need to ensure that User1 can enroll 150 Windows devices to Microsoft Intune. The solution must follow the principle of least privilege.

Which role should you assign to User1?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device Enrollment Manager</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Global Administrator</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Intune Service Administrator</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>no role assignment</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>A Device Enrollment Manager is a non-administrative account that can enroll up to 1000 devices.
Intune Service Administrators and Global Administrators would be granted more permissions than required. No role assignment is also incorrect. Standard users can enroll a maximum of 15 devices.</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>105</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 500 Windows 11 devices that are managed by using Microsoft Intune.

You need to deploy a Conditional Access policy that will ensure that users can only access the subscription from Windows devices that have BitLocker enabled.

What should you do first?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a Compliance policy.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a Device Configuration policy.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create an App Protection policy.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enable jailbreak detection.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>In order to ensure that users can only access your subscription from Windows devices with BitLocker enabled, you need to mark devices as compliant or not compliant by using a device Compliance policy as a first step.
[Create device compliance policies in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/create-compliance-policy]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>106</No>
          <Text>Your company is planning to deploy a new set of Windows devices to the sales team. These devices need to be pre-configured with specific security settings and applications before being distributed to users.

How should you automate the configuration process to ensure consistency and reduce manual effort?

Each correct answer is part of the solution. What two actions should you take?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>69</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a device configuration profile in Intune and assign it to the sales team devices.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enable BitLocker encryption on each device manually.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Manually install the required applications on each device.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Set up a Local Administrative Password Solution (LAPS) for the devices.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use Windows Autopilot to pre-configure the devices.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Creating a device configuration profile in Intune and assigning it to the sales team devices (A) ensures that all devices receive consistent security settings, automating part of the configuration process. Using Windows Autopilot to pre-configure the devices (E) automates the deployment, including the installation of required applications and settings, ensuring consistency while reducing manual effort. Enabling BitLocker encryption manually (B) and manually installing applications (C) are labor-intensive processes that do not align with the goal of automation. Setting up a Local Administrative Password Solution (LAPS) (D) manages admin passwords but does not assist in pre-configuring devices with security settings and applications.
[Manage mobile devices with Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/enroll-devices-use-intune/2-manage-mobile-devices-intune] &amp; [Deploy applications with Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/deploy-applications/2-deploy-applications-intune] &amp; [Manage and secure devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/fundamentals/manage-devices]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>107</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription that contains devices that run Windows 11.

All the devices are enrolled in Microsoft Intune.

You need to ensure that the devices use Delivery Optimization when installing Windows updates.

What should you configure in Intune?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>device configuration profile</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>feature updates for Windows 10 and later</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>quality updates for Windows 10 and later</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>update ring for Windows 10 and later</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Delivery Optimization reduces bandwidth consumption when devices download applications and updates. You can configure Delivery Optimization by using a device configuration profile and selecting the Delivery Optimization template.
[Delivery Optimization settings for Windows devices in Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/configuration/delivery-optimization-windows]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>108</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 100 Windows devices that are enrolled in Microsoft Intune.

You notice an update has caused an issue with an existing application.

You need to pause the update ring.

What is the maximum amount of time the update ring can be paused?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>35 Days</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>7 Days</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>28 Days</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>365 Days</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>35 days is correct. The maximum amount of time an update ring can be paused is 35 days.
[Configure Update rings for Windows 10 and later policy in Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/protect/windows-10-update-rings]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>109</No>
          <Text>Your company is transitioning to a cloud-first infrastructure and wants to ensure that all devices accessing their resources are compliant with their security policies. They have a mix of organization-owned and user-owned devices, including Windows, iOS, and Android devices.

You need to configure the devices to join Microsoft Entra ID and ensure they comply with the organization's security policies.

Each correct answer presents part of the solution. Which two actions should you perform?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>67</char>
            <char>68</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure the devices to use local accounts only.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Disable Conditional Access policies.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enroll the devices in Microsoft Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Register the devices to Microsoft Entra ID.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use a third-party MDM solution.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Enroll the devices in Microsoft Intune to manage and enforce compliance policies. Register the devices to Microsoft Entra ID to enable access to organizational resources. Configuring devices to use local accounts only would not provide the necessary access to resources. Disabling Conditional Access policies would reduce security. Using a third-party MDM solution is not necessary when Microsoft Intune can be used.
[Use Microsoft Entra join with automatic MDM enrollment - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/implement-dynamic-deployment/5-use-azure-ad-join-automatic-mobile-device-management-enrollment] &amp; [Examine Microsoft Entra join prerequisites limitations and benefits - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/administer-device-authentication/3-examine-azure-active-directory-join-prerequisites-limitations-benefits] &amp; [What are Microsoft Entra registered devices? - Microsoft Entra ID | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/entra/identity/devices/concept-device-registration]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>110</No>
          <Text>Your company plans to deploy Android devices for field workers. These devices need to be fully managed and restricted to work-related applications only.

You need to configure the enrollment profiles for these Android devices.

Each correct answer contributes to the solution. Which two actions should you take?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>66</char>
            <char>69</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure a compliance policy to restrict access to personal applications.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Connect your Intune tenant account to your Managed Google Play account.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a Device Enrollment Manager (DEM) account for the field workers.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enable automatic enrollment for Android devices in Microsoft Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Set up an Android Enterprise fully managed enrollment profile in Microsoft Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Setting up an Android Enterprise fully managed enrollment profile (E) ensures that the devices are fully managed and restricted to work-related applications. Connecting the Intune tenant account to the Managed Google Play account (B) is necessary for managing Android Enterprise devices. Creating a DEM account (C) is not relevant for this scenario, as it is not suitable for fully managed corporate devices. Enabling automatic enrollment (D) is not applicable for Android devices in this context. Configuring a compliance policy (A) is a separate task and does not directly relate to the initial enrollment configuration.
[Enroll devices using Microsoft Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/enroll-devices-use-intune/] &amp; [Tutorial - Use Apple Business Manager to enroll iOS/iPadOS devices in Intune - Microsoft Intune | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/enrollment/tutorial-use-device-enrollment-program-enroll-ios]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>111</No>
          <Text>Your company is planning to deploy Windows Hello for Business in a hybrid environment using both on-premises Active Directory and Microsoft Entra ID. They want to ensure a seamless deployment without conflicts between Group Policy and Intune settings.

How should you configure the devices to implement Windows Hello for Business in this hybrid environment?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Configure Windows Hello for Business settings in both Intune and Group Policy without any coordination.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Disable Windows Hello for Business in Intune and use only on-premises AD DS settings.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use Intune to manage Windows Hello for Business settings and ensure no overlapping settings with Group Policy.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use only Group Policy to manage Windows Hello for Business settings.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Using Intune to manage Windows Hello for Business settings and ensuring no overlapping settings with Group Policy (C) is the correct solution because it allows for centralized management in a hybrid environment and avoids conflicts between Group Policy and Intune settings. Configuring settings in both Intune and Group Policy without coordination (A) could lead to conflicts, making the deployment inconsistent. Disabling Windows Hello for Business in Intune and using only on-premises AD DS settings (B) limits cloud management capabilities, reducing the flexibility and effectiveness of the deployment. Using only Group Policy (D) restricts the ability to manage devices through Intune, which is essential in a hybrid environment where cloud-based management is needed.
[MD-102 1-Protect identities in Microsoft Entra ID - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/protect-identities-azure-acative-directory/] &amp; [Windows Hello for Business overview | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/windows/security/identity-protection/hello-for-business/]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>112</No>
          <Text>You plan to deploy 25 new Windows 11 devices that will be used by customers to browse the internet in a public location.

You need to recommend a Windows Autopilot mode for the deployment.

What should you recommend?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Windows Autopilot for existing devices</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Windows Autopilot Reset</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Windows Autopilot self-deploying mode</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Windows Autopilot user-driven mode</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Only self-deploying mode focusses directly on the kiosk mode requirement in the question as you can deploy the Kiosk Browser.
[Windows Autopilot self-deploying mode (Public Preview) | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/autopilot/self-deploying]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>113</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E3 subscription that includes 500 devices and uses Microsoft Intune. The devices run Windows 10 22H2 and are configured with Windows Recovery Environment.

You need to deploy Windows Autopilot. The solution must minimize the time taken to revert devices to a business-ready state.

What should you do first?</Text>
          <Answer>65</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a deployment profile.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create a dynamic device group.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Enable the DisableAutomaticReDeploymentCredentials policy.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Manually register the devices with Windows Autopilot.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>The first step is to create a deployment profile that converts all targeted devices to Autopilot devices.
You cannot change or reset the machines without being an Autopilot machine. Manually registering with Autopilot requires capturing the hardware hash of each machine. The DisableAutomaticReDeploymentCredentials policy can be configured after the deployment profile and a dynamic device group can be used to target the deployment profile.
[Windows Autopilot Reset | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/autopilot/windows-autopilot-reset] &amp; [Configure Autopilot profiles | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/autopilot/profiles]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>114</No>
          <Text>Your company is planning to deploy Windows 11 to its global workforce using a zero-touch deployment method. The company has a mix of new and existing devices that need to be configured with the same set of applications and security policies. The goal is to ensure that the deployment process is seamless and requires minimal user interaction.

Which deployment method and settings should you choose to achieve this goal?

Each correct answer presents part of the solution. What two actions should you perform?</Text>
          <Answer>0</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>true</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Answers>
            <char>65</char>
            <char>67</char>
          </Answers>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Create an Enrollment Status Page (ESP) in Microsoft Intune.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Deploy Windows 11 using USB drives.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Implement Windows Autopilot for new devices.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Manually install applications on each device.</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Use provisioning packages for all devices.</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Creating an Enrollment Status Page (ESP) in Microsoft Intune (A) is correct because ESP ensures that devices are fully configured with required applications and security policies before users can access them. This helps achieve a zero-touch deployment by verifying the configuration is complete without user intervention. Implementing Windows Autopilot for new devices (C) is also correct because Autopilot automates the deployment and configuration of new devices, enrolling them in Intune and ensuring they are pre-configured with necessary settings, applications, and policies. This reduces manual effort and provides a seamless, zero-touch deployment experience. Deploying Windows 11 using USB drives (B) is incorrect because this method is manual and contradicts the goal of automation. Manually installing applications on each device (D) is incorrect because it increases administrative overhead and does not align with the zero-touch deployment approach. Using provisioning packages for all devices (E) is incorrect because, while useful in certain cases, provisioning packages are not the most scalable or automated solution for a global deployment compared to Windows Autopilot.
[Explore Windows Security Center - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/manage-defender-windows-client/2-explore-windows-security-center] &amp; [Explore Windows 365 - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/manage-windows-365/2-explore-windows-365] &amp; [Windows 11 overview for administrators | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/windows/whats-new/windows-11-overview]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>115</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 E5 subscription that uses Microsoft Intune.

You have the following devices enrolled in Intune:

    Device1: Windows 11

    Device2: Android

    Device3: iOS

You plan to implement Remediations in Intune to detect and fix common support issues.

On which devices can you use Remediations?</Text>
          <Answer>68</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 and Device2 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 and Device3 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1, Device2, and Device3</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device1 only</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>69</Alphabet>
              <Text>Device2 and Device3 only</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Remediations require that devices run Windows 11 Enterprise or Windows 10 Enterprise. Remediations are implemented by creating scripting package(s) and are inapplicable to Android and iOS devices.
[Remediations | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/mem/intune/fundamentals/remediations]</Explanation>
        </Question>
        <Question>
          <No>116</No>
          <Text>You have a Microsoft 365 subscription that includes 500 Windows 11 devices that are enrolled in Microsoft Intune.

You create a new configuration profile and deploy it to all Windows 11 devices.

What is the maximum amount of time it may take for a device to apply the new configuration profile?</Text>
          <Answer>67</Answer>
          <IsMultipleChoice>false</IsMultipleChoice>
          <Options>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>65</Alphabet>
              <Text>5 minutes</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>66</Alphabet>
              <Text>60 minutes</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>67</Alphabet>
              <Text>8 hours</Text>
            </Option>
            <Option>
              <Alphabet>68</Alphabet>
              <Text>24 hours</Text>
            </Option>
          </Options>
          <Explanation>Windows devices which have not been recently enrolled will check-in every 8 hours.
Recently enrolled Windows devices checked in more regularly (Every 3 minutes for 30 minutes), however machines that have not enrolled recently will not.
[Manage device sync in Intune - Training | Microsoft Learn: https://learn.microsoft.com/training/modules/monitor-device-profiles/3-manage-device-sync-intune]</Explanation>
        </Question>
      </Questions>
    </Section>
  </Sections>
</Exam>